[{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e50"},"rt":16331,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66125,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"O 5K U A A O K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e51"},"rt":17567,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83803,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E 6D D J 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e52"},"rt":22824,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106773,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"6F F A C A Z Z A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e53"},"rt":4102,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":110994,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"4K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e54"},"rt":2098,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113188,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e56"},"rt":6536,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":122864,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"F E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e57"},"rt":24062,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147248,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B B F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e58"},"rt":6926,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154270,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"5H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e59"},"rt":11565,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":165969,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F 4F F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e5a"},"rt":5268,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171453,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"B O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e5b"},"rt":2338,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173916,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e5c"},"rt":5712,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179732,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e5d"},"rt":4159,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":184003,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"Z D J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e5e"},"rt":3400,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187497,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e5f"},"rt":2265,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189873,"subject":"P5TGP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e70"},"rt":3644,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":20028,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e71"},"rt":5887,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":26059,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"5E E E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e72"},"rt":10887,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":37083,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"11 AM10 AMC C A A C C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e73"},"rt":21156,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":58344,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A A Z A Z F F H H U 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e74"},"rt":23674,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82140,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"O O I O O Z F U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e76"},"rt":6465,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":89805,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e77"},"rt":7072,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96987,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e78"},"rt":23814,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120913,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B E B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e79"},"rt":6870,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":127891,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e7a"},"rt":3336,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131329,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e7b"},"rt":6733,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138174,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e7c"},"rt":3323,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141690,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e7d"},"rt":14002,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":155818,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"O Z 04 PMX B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e7e"},"rt":37343,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193276,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"E E E B B M M X X X X X C E E F B B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e7f"},"rt":34543,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228221,"subject":"YM960","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43081","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M M C C G B E E G E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e90"},"rt":6865,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":17933,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e91"},"rt":6449,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":24470,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"Z F E E D E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e92"},"rt":128,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":24682,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e93"},"rt":10412,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":35185,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"03 PM04 PME E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e94"},"rt":24027,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59299,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"B K H I I I I O O O O O O O 12 PMO 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e96"},"rt":23052,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":86343,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"J 10 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PMD D B B E G G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e97"},"rt":6616,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":93044,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"5F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e98"},"rt":22788,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115919,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E F E G G G G E 05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e99"},"rt":10151,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":126187,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"O B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e9a"},"rt":28404,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154682,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B B F F B B B B F F F F F F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e9b"},"rt":5403,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160186,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"E D 04 PM03 PM01 PMB B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e9c"},"rt":2645,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162916,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e9d"},"rt":27807,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190819,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,X ","hovered":"X Z Z Z O B B F B M X X B B B J J J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e9e"},"rt":13692,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204629,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0e9f"},"rt":33290,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238040,"subject":"EUUV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38373","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O X J J M M M F B 11 AM02 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb0"},"rt":28217,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132076,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM11 AMA A 5A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb1"},"rt":9216,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141391,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb2"},"rt":14902,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156380,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C C 12 PMZ C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb3"},"rt":14979,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171451,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PMU U U 02 PM02 PMU U 04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb4"},"rt":88458,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260002,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"7I O I 12 PMC Z Z F H F F F U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb6"},"rt":16637,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":279128,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"08 AME E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb7"},"rt":42863,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322099,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"H C F B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb8"},"rt":39635,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361826,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F B B E B B J 10 AMI I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eb9"},"rt":19593,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":381520,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eba"},"rt":15437,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397046,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ebb"},"rt":8088,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405228,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"03 PM02 PMB B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ebc"},"rt":5087,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410404,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ebd"},"rt":25987,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":436483,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z X X B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ebe"},"rt":33020,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469599,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"11 AM02 PMB 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ebf"},"rt":121450,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591146,"subject":"9DK63","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34802","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"B F F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed0"},"rt":15302,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":45332,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed1"},"rt":8517,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53938,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed2"},"rt":15181,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69213,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"09 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed3"},"rt":27815,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97122,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"10 AM12 PMC C A U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed4"},"rt":20617,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117874,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O O I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed6"},"rt":6199,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":129373,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed7"},"rt":71506,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":201011,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"5C F I J J J I F B B B B F H H F I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed8"},"rt":38215,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239521,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"I G B E E I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ed9"},"rt":11923,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":251564,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"6J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eda"},"rt":6562,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258238,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0edb"},"rt":6863,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265194,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"212 PM12 PMM L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0edc"},"rt":9319,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274613,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"B B F F B B F G G G I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0edd"},"rt":24696,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299413,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"A H O L H H Z Z Z X O O O O X X X O Z F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ede"},"rt":7438,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306981,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PMX X X 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0edf"},"rt":16200,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323278,"subject":"ZKG07","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43056","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PMX X K K K G 6K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef0"},"rt":33290,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145730,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"5Z A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef1"},"rt":8020,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153842,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef2"},"rt":22439,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176358,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C 10 AMC C Z Z O O O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef3"},"rt":40510,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216954,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"E E H H U U U U 04 PM04 PM01 PM01 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef4"},"rt":30799,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247835,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"H I I I I O O U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef6"},"rt":7513,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261053,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef7"},"rt":13309,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274443,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"H F F B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef8"},"rt":22564,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297085,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"05 PMB B F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ef9"},"rt":11487,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":308656,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"8G I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0efa"},"rt":25553,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":334285,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0efb"},"rt":20056,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354418,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C M 12 PMB B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0efc"},"rt":11253,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365750,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0efd"},"rt":20052,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":385880,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"M Z X X X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0efe"},"rt":29310,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415268,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"X M M O B B B E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0eff"},"rt":58996,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474340,"subject":"MAFVW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"X F 12 PM01 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f10"},"rt":21179,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66879,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f11"},"rt":14023,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81169,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F U D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f12"},"rt":28226,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109736,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"O A C 10 AM10 AMC A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f13"},"rt":21530,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131589,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"3304 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f14"},"rt":100742,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232701,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"Z I J I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f16"},"rt":7596,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":245885,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f17"},"rt":10035,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256240,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f18"},"rt":99964,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356466,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G I I J G B B F B 03 PMB B O B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f19"},"rt":15121,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":371999,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f1a"},"rt":44847,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417193,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B F Z X X Z Z X X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f1b"},"rt":8818,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426395,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PM02 PMB B F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f1c"},"rt":5009,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431657,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"4B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f1d"},"rt":29356,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":461271,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"H Z Z F B X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f1e"},"rt":47754,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":509330,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f1f"},"rt":41353,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550981,"subject":"VPBE4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43001","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X X X X F J J J F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f30"},"rt":9502,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119246,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"5A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f31"},"rt":13341,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132720,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"K D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f32"},"rt":7259,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140119,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"H A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f33"},"rt":127742,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267986,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"O 04 PM04 PM03 PME I Z 03 PM04 PM04 PMU U U U U U A 11 AMA U U F F F H H J J J H 12 PMZ 01 PMU 04 PM04 PM04 PMF F O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f34"},"rt":234791,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":503108,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,U ","hovered":"I I I I U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f36"},"rt":7252,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":518418,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f37"},"rt":46643,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565209,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f38"},"rt":73503,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":638833,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E B F E E E E I I B B F F F J I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f39"},"rt":40561,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":679768,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I 10 AMI I I I I I B 12 PM12 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f3a"},"rt":152515,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":832434,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"J K F F F N 04 PMZ X B B X F F F E E B B B F F E F 02 PM01 PM12 PME C X X F B B M X X O O X B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f3b"},"rt":8883,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":841644,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f3c"},"rt":6532,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":848309,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f3d"},"rt":35880,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":884320,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"G X Z F B B X X Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f3e"},"rt":289058,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1173509,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"04 PMX B B B B F F E E E 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f3f"},"rt":97528,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1271406,"subject":"520AG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"29699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"H F X 02 PMM B E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f50"},"rt":43074,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299925,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AM11 AMA 12 PMA 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f51"},"rt":16803,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317103,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"K D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f52"},"rt":24514,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341884,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"3C C C 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f53"},"rt":140313,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482461,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PME E E E E D E E E E D E E D F U 02 PMZ U U F F Z Z Z H I O O O 12 PMO C A F F F F F H H 01 PM01 PMH 08 AMI I O 11 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f54"},"rt":154998,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":637749,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I O I A 11 AMO O I I 7A A 12 PMK K 02 PMU F F C C C C C C A A Z U U U U U U U U U F F F H 01 PMI O O O O 5O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f56"},"rt":12652,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":663255,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"5E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f57"},"rt":19373,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":682899,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F M B F F B F B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f58"},"rt":56435,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":739605,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E F B E E E E X X X X E X X X F F E 11 AM11 AME B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f59"},"rt":36604,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":776496,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I J B I I J J J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f5a"},"rt":69866,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":846644,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B B 12 PMF B B B B M M M B X F F O O 01 PM01 PM01 PME E E E E E E E G G M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f5b"},"rt":11276,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":858220,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"3F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f5c"},"rt":19630,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":878133,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F F B B 3F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f5d"},"rt":26244,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":904653,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"O Z Z O F X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f5e"},"rt":28391,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":933341,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"3X B C 01 PMC C C 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f5f"},"rt":63505,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":997122,"subject":"AJO1Q","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38961","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M M M M B 12 PMB F F F X X X F F F F F F F X X X X X F E E E E E 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f70"},"rt":36464,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141882,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"I C 611 AMA A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f71"},"rt":10694,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152664,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f72"},"rt":37038,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189844,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C C C C C C C A A A 10 AMZ Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f73"},"rt":184473,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374412,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMU 04 PM04 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f74"},"rt":100177,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474823,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I U F F I I 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f76"},"rt":8364,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":515195,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"6E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f77"},"rt":21793,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":537109,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f78"},"rt":65644,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":602849,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B B B F F B F E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f79"},"rt":23513,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":626567,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"E C J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f7a"},"rt":77757,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":704440,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z Z Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f7b"},"rt":22512,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":727151,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"502 PM01 PM12 PMB F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f7c"},"rt":7458,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":734699,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f7d"},"rt":64171,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":798949,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z X X X X X Z F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f7e"},"rt":76316,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":875486,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"7F F M 03 PM03 PMB 03 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f7f"},"rt":55882,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":931564,"subject":"LV82T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35324","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMX X 02 PM02 PMX X F E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f90"},"rt":7313,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34000,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z Z 12 PM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f91"},"rt":19533,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53663,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J D C C E E 04 PMD D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f92"},"rt":20571,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":74413,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"4I Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f93"},"rt":27793,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102427,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U U K K F 12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f94"},"rt":66523,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169135,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"O I 12 PMZ 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMF F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f96"},"rt":9511,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":181047,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f97"},"rt":21139,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202284,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F Z Z F F F B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f98"},"rt":50241,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":252685,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"4B I J J J J J M M B I O E I I G G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f99"},"rt":15282,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":268100,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f9a"},"rt":79717,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347926,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"F Z X X X O G E E G C C H F Z Z Z I M M O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f9b"},"rt":11671,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360243,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f9c"},"rt":5778,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366123,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f9d"},"rt":31874,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":398151,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"Z B C C X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f9e"},"rt":33124,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431374,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B O B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0f9f"},"rt":48275,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":479774,"subject":"MNLNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35897","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M 02 PMX B B F O B B F B B F X 02 PM12 PME G 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb0"},"rt":19570,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115615,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb1"},"rt":15628,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131343,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O D D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb2"},"rt":28252,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159692,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,I ","hovered":"C A A C 09 AM10 AMC O O O A A O I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb3"},"rt":8181,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167976,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PMU U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb4"},"rt":16697,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184775,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb6"},"rt":7798,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":194459,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"N E G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb7"},"rt":35125,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229677,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"Z M N N M M B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb8"},"rt":3811,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233626,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fb9"},"rt":12531,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":246260,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I J M M J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fba"},"rt":17533,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263892,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PMF Z Z Z Z B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fbb"},"rt":10695,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274710,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PMB B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fbc"},"rt":5302,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280110,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fbd"},"rt":14750,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":294959,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fbe"},"rt":11335,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306411,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"04 PM03 PMM B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fbf"},"rt":7766,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314292,"subject":"MTFDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38372","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd0"},"rt":35812,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98709,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"708 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMA Z Z A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd1"},"rt":41626,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140425,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"4D D D F A 7I D J J H E J 03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd2"},"rt":20193,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160710,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"H H C 11 AMA A A C C 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd3"},"rt":11247,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172047,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd4"},"rt":142880,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315180,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"I I I U U I I I I O O O O I I I I I I O O O A O 11 AMF F O O O O F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd6"},"rt":10545,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":339229,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd7"},"rt":22670,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361993,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd8"},"rt":66877,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428984,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B B B B B B F B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fd9"},"rt":41725,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":470953,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I J J J J I I B B B B J J I J 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fda"},"rt":6928,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477972,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F F F E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fdb"},"rt":8342,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486409,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"09 AM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fdc"},"rt":11956,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498622,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"6F F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fdd"},"rt":84761,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":583472,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"Z B L Z Z Z Z 04 PM04 PMO C C G G C 10 AM10 AM10 AMM H Z 02 PM02 PM02 PMZ B F F E E E C O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fde"},"rt":11825,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":595550,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"J X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fdf"},"rt":23512,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619149,"subject":"K4OUL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38107","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X X X X X X X K X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff0"},"rt":17548,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":873458,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F 11 AMA A A A A O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff1"},"rt":8057,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":881629,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff2"},"rt":14277,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":896076,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"K K C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff3"},"rt":51229,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":947416,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F 4Z Z A O O Z O O U 02 PM03 PM04 PMU F C F C J J F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff4"},"rt":59806,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1007310,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"I O F F 01 PM02 PM01 PMF O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff6"},"rt":5126,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1024400,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff7"},"rt":19594,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1044176,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff8"},"rt":27254,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1071588,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"7I F F B E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ff9"},"rt":22292,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1093971,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ffa"},"rt":24387,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1118692,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F F 04 PM04 PMF E E I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ffb"},"rt":7531,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1126346,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"X B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ffc"},"rt":15112,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1141547,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B C C F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ffd"},"rt":53908,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1195550,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"6F Z H Z Z Z F O O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0ffe"},"rt":21477,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1217118,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"03 PMB B F X J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e0fff"},"rt":38732,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1256015,"subject":"SESUV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38579","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1010"},"rt":19049,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122986,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AM010 AM11 AM11 AMA A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1011"},"rt":14591,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137764,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"U E E E E 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1012"},"rt":33062,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":170953,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"5E U Z C C C Z U U U Z 08 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1013"},"rt":64511,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235581,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,U ","hovered":"01 PM12 PM10 AM10 AMC C C C C C A A Z Z F F U O K K H I I D D G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1014"},"rt":74253,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310293,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"01 PM12 PMZ U U U 10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM06 PMU F U Z Z A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1016"},"rt":10684,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":332392,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"09 AMI E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1017"},"rt":40819,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":373323,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"6C F F J B B B B B B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1018"},"rt":135911,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":509349,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L B B I I I B J M M M M M B B B X X B 12 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMB F F B B B J J J J J I J 09 AMI 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PMX 03 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1019"},"rt":122927,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":632695,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J J J I B B J 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PMJ J J J J I J J J J I I J I 4L D N J I 3J J B B F F E E E F B B B F F B I J J J J B B B O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e101a"},"rt":31272,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":664391,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"4F F Z 04 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e101b"},"rt":15610,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":680449,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PMM M M M M 12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMB F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e101c"},"rt":12142,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":693028,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B F F I 2J F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e101d"},"rt":30509,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":723653,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z Z X 02 PM03 PM04 PMO B B B B F F F F Z Z F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e101e"},"rt":36497,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":760270,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMO B 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMB B B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e101f"},"rt":36025,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":796409,"subject":"AEEBQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X X 01 PMM J J I I B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1030"},"rt":18219,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84945,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1031"},"rt":4700,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89771,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1032"},"rt":7623,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97506,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1033"},"rt":8138,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105754,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1034"},"rt":6040,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111902,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1036"},"rt":27906,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":142741,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"5G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1037"},"rt":2777,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145636,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ","hovered":"L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1038"},"rt":3406,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":149172,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"P K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1039"},"rt":7963,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":157244,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e103a"},"rt":4796,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162153,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e103b"},"rt":2957,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165222,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P ","hovered":"P P P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e103c"},"rt":3048,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168385,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e103d"},"rt":3446,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":171940,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e103e"},"rt":17242,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189306,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e103f"},"rt":2712,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192149,"subject":"C1TTY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43299","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1050"},"rt":12851,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":32290,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"U K 12 PMA A A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1051"},"rt":4210,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":36604,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1052"},"rt":15707,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":52451,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,I ","hovered":"H C C A A U U A U C A Z A Z Z O O I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1053"},"rt":18060,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70616,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,U ","hovered":"611 AM10 AM09 AMU U U U F F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1054"},"rt":12833,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83540,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1056"},"rt":6751,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":93191,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"4E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1057"},"rt":13531,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106825,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"E J F F F F B B B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1058"},"rt":22515,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129438,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G J J J J I L B E E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1059"},"rt":15924,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":145464,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"8H H A J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e105a"},"rt":11959,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157527,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"I F Z X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e105b"},"rt":6151,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163772,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e105c"},"rt":5296,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169155,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e105d"},"rt":30461,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":199711,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B O X Z O O Z Z Z O O Z Z X X X Z B B J J J I O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e105e"},"rt":34541,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234344,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e105f"},"rt":22282,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256717,"subject":"Z84ZV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41634","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"03 PM02 PMX X X X X X X X F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1070"},"rt":23210,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187842,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A 11 AM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1071"},"rt":11013,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198973,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1072"},"rt":20236,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219349,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"5H H H H H C C A Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1073"},"rt":28777,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248239,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A U U C U U F U Z Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1074"},"rt":97220,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345604,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1076"},"rt":23480,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":376577,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1077"},"rt":15115,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391789,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1078"},"rt":41478,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":433365,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":8,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ,H ,I ,J ,N ,O ,Z ","hovered":"6B B E I I J J I I I J J J J J J X X X O O H Z Z Z N D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1079"},"rt":72705,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506390,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,M ","hovered":"I J B O M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e107a"},"rt":48014,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554674,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F Z Z Z X X Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e107b"},"rt":7431,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562267,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e107c"},"rt":8576,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":571055,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e107d"},"rt":20733,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":592037,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"C Z Z Z F B B O X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e107e"},"rt":61638,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":653920,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4B 04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e107f"},"rt":140032,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":794345,"subject":"K83ZA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42756","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"12 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMF F 03 PM02 PMF 02 PMB B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1090"},"rt":23351,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41899,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1091"},"rt":17004,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":58997,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O Z Z J J J E E J J K E 05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1092"},"rt":10152,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69241,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C C C A A A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1093"},"rt":77983,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147321,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"3H O 03 PM04 PME U 02 PM02 PM01 PMZ A A A 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1094"},"rt":85881,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233530,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"O I I O O 12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMH I 12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMO 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMI 01 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM02 PM02 PM03 PME E E Z F 01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1096"},"rt":10311,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":246643,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1097"},"rt":12800,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259535,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"3M F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1098"},"rt":33046,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292675,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ,X ","hovered":"H X 02 PM03 PM03 PMM M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1099"},"rt":19590,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":312413,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I I B B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e109a"},"rt":32454,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344956,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B B B 12 PM12 PM03 PM04 PMJ M M X X O B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e109b"},"rt":10982,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356398,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"11 AM12 PMB B F B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e109c"},"rt":5152,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361642,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e109d"},"rt":29123,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":390853,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B B F B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e109e"},"rt":19284,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410234,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMB B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e109f"},"rt":60587,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470909,"subject":"F6V09","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37410","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"03 PM02 PM02 PMM M M X 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b0"},"rt":22026,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182155,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"011 AMA A 11 AM11 AM10 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b1"},"rt":12224,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194472,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"5E E E E 04 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b2"},"rt":14932,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209508,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"0Z Z 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b3"},"rt":47005,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256627,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A U U U F O A 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b4"},"rt":112692,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369422,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F I I 07 PM08 PM12 PM03 PMU U U U U U F U 03 PMF H H U 02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMU F 01 PM12 PMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b6"},"rt":7378,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":384009,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"5E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b7"},"rt":28344,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412517,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b8"},"rt":42374,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454990,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J X X B B X X X X X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10b9"},"rt":19342,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":474423,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10ba"},"rt":39577,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514089,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"I 05 PM04 PM04 PMX X X X X F F E 11 AM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10bb"},"rt":10918,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525096,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J M M B B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10bc"},"rt":9010,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534196,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"2B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10bd"},"rt":34199,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":568483,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMF F F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10be"},"rt":31226,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":599799,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"11 AMB B 12 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10bf"},"rt":25191,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":625080,"subject":"YCA39","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"B B F 01 PM02 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d0"},"rt":4440,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160970,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d1"},"rt":3544,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164620,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d2"},"rt":8034,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172761,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d3"},"rt":290225,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463087,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"O K 04 PMU A F H K F F F F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d4"},"rt":61533,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524928,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"6I I I 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMD I I I Z A O O I U U A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d6"},"rt":6519,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":533334,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d7"},"rt":14598,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":548034,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"5Z H F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d8"},"rt":53094,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":601232,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E G F B B B B X X O E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10d9"},"rt":12540,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":613873,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"O L G G F J J I I I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10da"},"rt":21690,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":635767,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10db"},"rt":19447,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":655323,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"911G Z M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10dc"},"rt":14907,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":670337,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"H H G B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10dd"},"rt":26010,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":696449,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z H G G F X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10de"},"rt":14733,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":711283,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"H O 03 PMO O O O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10df"},"rt":21808,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":733383,"subject":"FPY8N","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40826","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"B O N O X X X F X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f0"},"rt":15154,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43844,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3I H H H O H J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f1"},"rt":21550,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":65555,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"6D D D D J J D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f2"},"rt":17761,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83505,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f3"},"rt":25358,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109337,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f4"},"rt":15273,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124737,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"K H H J H H H J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f6"},"rt":7850,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":134529,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"1E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f7"},"rt":17236,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151905,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,Z ","hovered":"B F F B H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f8"},"rt":42896,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195560,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"4Z Z H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10f9"},"rt":18113,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":213883,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"I B I I I E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10fa"},"rt":11606,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225720,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10fb"},"rt":17654,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243489,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"10 AM11 AMB B F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10fc"},"rt":5197,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248809,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10fd"},"rt":39331,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":288264,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,H ","hovered":"2N N N Z Z H H H L C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10fe"},"rt":30418,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":318840,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,O ","hovered":"03 PM03 PMO B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e10ff"},"rt":23381,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342384,"subject":"4XWJ9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43265","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"X X X X X K O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1110"},"rt":15205,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48831,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"O F 10 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1111"},"rt":11085,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60026,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"Z D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1112"},"rt":31173,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":91326,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"K O C A A A C C C A U E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1113"},"rt":17011,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108443,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"F F F 03 PM04 PMU A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1114"},"rt":13731,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122393,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"I I O O K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1116"},"rt":15423,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":142978,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1117"},"rt":17521,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160742,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B C C C B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1118"},"rt":54036,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214894,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"C F X X M M M M M M M J J X X X K K X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1119"},"rt":17637,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":232659,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"C O X M I I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e111a"},"rt":8518,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241642,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"B F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e111b"},"rt":6414,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248259,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e111c"},"rt":12877,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261326,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"06 PM04 PMC G F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e111d"},"rt":24087,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":285508,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"Z Z H H P P K K K E K Z Z M J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e111e"},"rt":14969,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300576,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,I ,O ","hovered":"I I B B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e111f"},"rt":14432,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315108,"subject":"0NEOZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38024","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,X ","hovered":"J J J J J X 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1130"},"rt":57812,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211390,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"111 AM01 PM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1131"},"rt":12189,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223727,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1132"},"rt":19929,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243765,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM01 PMZ C A O O A A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1133"},"rt":103992,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347863,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ","hovered":"01 PM11 AM03 PMG U C 09 AM11 AMD D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1134"},"rt":29168,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377307,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ,E ","hovered":"I H H E K O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1136"},"rt":8764,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":422098,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I E E G 6G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1137"},"rt":67496,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":489712,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"2B 4F F F Z Z O Z Z B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1138"},"rt":51425,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541403,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1139"},"rt":34677,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":576182,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B B J I I I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e113a"},"rt":20628,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":596929,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e113b"},"rt":9977,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607042,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e113c"},"rt":38298,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":645469,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B F F F Z Z X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e113d"},"rt":59343,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":704909,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"G Z Z F F F Z L L L F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e113e"},"rt":55954,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":760958,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMO I I J B 03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMG G 03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e113f"},"rt":17627,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":778689,"subject":"2ZH12","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43264","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"02 PM02 PMK X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1150"},"rt":15427,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":121863,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1151"},"rt":34724,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156691,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,D ","hovered":"O D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1152"},"rt":17253,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174057,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"H A 11 AM11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1153"},"rt":8628,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182790,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM04 PMH H H O 5H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1154"},"rt":72557,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255458,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"I 11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1156"},"rt":8651,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269990,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"5E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1157"},"rt":26555,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296657,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"M X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1158"},"rt":51538,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348308,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"E O O H H O O X O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1159"},"rt":22308,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370725,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J J E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e115a"},"rt":7384,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378224,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e115b"},"rt":8268,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386607,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"12 PMM M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e115c"},"rt":12936,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399657,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e115d"},"rt":10588,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":410354,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"X Z F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e115e"},"rt":14923,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425389,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"I 03 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e115f"},"rt":9825,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435321,"subject":"5CNJR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28191","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PMX X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1170"},"rt":29797,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96411,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1171"},"rt":8537,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105058,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1172"},"rt":15057,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120372,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"6C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1173"},"rt":7035,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127507,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1174"},"rt":91210,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218819,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"H H I O F F O A A O O I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1176"},"rt":8225,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":234498,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1177"},"rt":48028,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":282624,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"F F B B B F B B B O O X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1178"},"rt":62138,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345065,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"B B B B B F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1179"},"rt":50280,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":395641,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H B J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e117a"},"rt":6250,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402310,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e117b"},"rt":10458,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413356,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"M L L L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e117c"},"rt":6307,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419853,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"2B G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e117d"},"rt":9977,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":429931,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"4Z Z F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e117e"},"rt":6767,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436795,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e117f"},"rt":15347,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452441,"subject":"3TPYE","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32618","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"02 PMX X X K C X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1190"},"rt":29589,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142018,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"2A 11 AM01 PM09 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1191"},"rt":10190,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152313,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D D E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1192"},"rt":20165,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172577,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"U C C Z Z Z Z Z 2C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1193"},"rt":31125,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203802,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A 04 PMU U U U 03 PM04 PMF Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1194"},"rt":109111,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313015,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I I 11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PMI O O 12 PM12 PMU I I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1196"},"rt":10347,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":331857,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"457E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1197"},"rt":23363,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":355321,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1198"},"rt":41828,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397248,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"7L B M M M B B B B B F B B B E J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1199"},"rt":25668,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423030,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"L J I 10 AM10 AMJ I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e119a"},"rt":22809,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445946,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F O O O X M F E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e119b"},"rt":6694,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452744,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PMB B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e119c"},"rt":12145,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464987,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e119d"},"rt":37899,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":502985,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"6F 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMZ Z 04 PMZ Z O X X M X X C F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e119e"},"rt":25878,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528965,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"J 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMB B B B 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e119f"},"rt":66227,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":595296,"subject":"F91EW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35783","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"02 PMM M B B F E I I I E 11 AME E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b0"},"rt":40030,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1636493,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"H 411 AMA A 6A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b1"},"rt":8747,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1645347,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b2"},"rt":119640,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1765077,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ","hovered":"H K 04 PME D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b3"},"rt":103827,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1869186,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"04 PM08 AM09 AMC 04 PMD E E K E E D D B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b4"},"rt":17670,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1887169,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U U U U A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b6"},"rt":27649,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1930694,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,E ,G ,K ,L ,P ","hovered":"E G G L L A P P K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b7"},"rt":25527,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1956316,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b8"},"rt":53386,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2009798,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,H ,N ,Z ","hovered":"G G B B B B I J J I J N D Z Z H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11b9"},"rt":64470,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2074442,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11ba"},"rt":62144,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2136869,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11bb"},"rt":12059,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2149217,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"X 12 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11bc"},"rt":7058,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2156452,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11bd"},"rt":26202,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2182747,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ,N ","hovered":"Z H H H N N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11be"},"rt":37423,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2220266,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"02 PMX M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11bf"},"rt":31651,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2252008,"subject":"9XRXZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42754","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"C C M M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d0"},"rt":18158,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53526,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PMC C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d1"},"rt":15516,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69149,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d2"},"rt":12257,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81523,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"5C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d3"},"rt":41302,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":123103,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,U ","hovered":"12 PM12 PMO O O U U U I O O F F F F 12 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d4"},"rt":61088,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184417,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,H ","hovered":"I I I 03 PM03 PMH J H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d6"},"rt":9193,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":197739,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"A E E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d7"},"rt":14191,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212825,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d8"},"rt":34620,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247575,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"K K G X X B X X B B E E C G G B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11d9"},"rt":18893,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":266587,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"6I J I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11da"},"rt":6662,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273350,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11db"},"rt":5322,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278771,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"02 PM12 PM12 PMB B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11dc"},"rt":12644,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291672,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11dd"},"rt":111154,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":402947,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z O Z Z Z O C O O C G C C G Z Z G O O O C G O O 04 PMC O O 04 PM04 PMC G G G C C O 04 PMG G C C G G C O O O O O Z Z 11 AMX X B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11de"},"rt":36269,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439639,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM11 AM10 AM10 AMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11df"},"rt":75047,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514789,"subject":"61XQA","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38676","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"Z F F E 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f0"},"rt":3703,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":21262,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f1"},"rt":695,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":22046,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f2"},"rt":13607,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":35743,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"7G F H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f3"},"rt":1831,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":37664,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f4"},"rt":1727,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":39480,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f6"},"rt":1977,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":42441,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f7"},"rt":1677,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":44210,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"5F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f8"},"rt":7746,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":52045,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11f9"},"rt":1763,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":53902,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11fa"},"rt":2355,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":56355,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11fb"},"rt":1756,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":58212,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11fc"},"rt":3883,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62194,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11fd"},"rt":1832,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":64123,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"5G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11fe"},"rt":3776,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":67991,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e11ff"},"rt":2959,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71040,"subject":"X44Y4","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42228","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1210"},"rt":18324,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":47437,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"409 AM09 AM11 AMA A A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1211"},"rt":29194,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76723,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D D E E E D 608 PM08 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1212"},"rt":70085,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146899,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"U A C C C C 11 AMA A A C C 11 AM10 AMC C C C C A A F F 10 AM09 AM08 AM0008 AM09 AMC C A O O O C C C C A A A O O Z Z O O O C C A C C C C Z D E F C C C C Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1213"},"rt":71570,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218771,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM04 PMU U F F F F O O O I F F F F F F F F 04 PM04 PMF F 12 PM12 PMC A A A A K K H H J A 01 PMO 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1214"},"rt":46033,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265086,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3F I O O 06 PM06 PM06 PM06 PMB B G G K U U U U U K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1216"},"rt":6851,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275442,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"C E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1217"},"rt":18158,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293683,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"5F B B B B B B B B B B B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1218"},"rt":40455,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":334222,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C E B B E E B X X X X 04 PMF X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1219"},"rt":18351,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352655,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"E F J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e121a"},"rt":23749,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":376489,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F F F F F F B B 12 PM03 PMX X 04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e121b"},"rt":8850,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385428,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F X 02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM10 AM11 AM12 PMB B F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e121c"},"rt":6022,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391535,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"3B B B B 3B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e121d"},"rt":17640,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":409268,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z 04 PMX X O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e121e"},"rt":11246,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420602,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PMM B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e121f"},"rt":33150,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":453848,"subject":"XNRRS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32055","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M 01 PM02 PMX X E 11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMB E 11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMB B B B B F F B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1230"},"rt":37191,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":91251,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"C C C 2F C C C C F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1231"},"rt":7842,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99279,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"C K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1232"},"rt":12227,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111669,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"2C A F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1233"},"rt":8295,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120138,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"03 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1234"},"rt":19919,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140225,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1236"},"rt":6829,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":154831,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"J E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1237"},"rt":26426,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181352,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"5F X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1238"},"rt":34676,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216122,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1239"},"rt":42748,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":258961,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I E E J J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e123a"},"rt":11432,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270484,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F F E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e123b"},"rt":6902,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277479,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"J 12 PMM M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e123c"},"rt":8671,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286257,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F G G 5L L G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e123d"},"rt":15004,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":301351,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"Z F F F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e123e"},"rt":5676,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307115,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e123f"},"rt":20025,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327228,"subject":"N8UV7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42759","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"2X X X X X K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1250"},"rt":76654,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174836,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"A A C A F A Z 02 PM12 PMA F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1251"},"rt":21632,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196805,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1252"},"rt":15814,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212698,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"H C C C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1253"},"rt":68352,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281207,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H H H H H H H U 11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMA A A A A 10 AMA H 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1254"},"rt":29953,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311519,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1256"},"rt":10321,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":328545,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1257"},"rt":17959,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346631,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"C C C C H O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1258"},"rt":37105,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383903,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"X B B B B B B B F F G G I I E F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1259"},"rt":53385,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":437471,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J J J J J J B B I I J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e125a"},"rt":14551,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452173,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E B F F F F F E 6E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e125b"},"rt":9552,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461821,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"M M M M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e125c"},"rt":5721,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467624,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e125d"},"rt":18005,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":485736,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"Z Z Z B F F O F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e125e"},"rt":10919,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496775,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"5E G C C X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e125f"},"rt":15945,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":512860,"subject":"H1PJT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37211","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"5X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1270"},"rt":21104,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70449,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"33611 AMA 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1271"},"rt":5738,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76277,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A A H D D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1272"},"rt":8675,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85044,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1273"},"rt":28956,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114090,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"6O F 05 PM04 PME F A C C C C A A C F 04 PMH O O H H 04 PMB B U 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1274"},"rt":16445,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130623,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1276"},"rt":4564,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":141949,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E 5G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1277"},"rt":13914,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155949,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1278"},"rt":73273,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229313,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"6E E E B B B N X X 03 PMX X X X X 03 PM02 PMM M M B M M J I J J J I J J J J J J B B E E F F 02 PMB B B B J E E E G G G 10 AMF F G O O O G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1279"},"rt":36536,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":266118,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I E F F E E J J I J J J I I E E E E I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e127a"},"rt":10436,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276647,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C F F 02 PMF F E I F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e127b"},"rt":16576,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293314,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"X 01 PM12 PMM M L L M M M L L L D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e127c"},"rt":14500,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307904,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"B B B F F F G G G G G G C C C 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e127d"},"rt":10482,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":318554,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"7O N D N Z F F E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e127e"},"rt":10881,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329530,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"M 01 PM02 PMX X X X X 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e127f"},"rt":8980,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338598,"subject":"7VUGQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"26423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"02 PM01 PM02 PMX X K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1290"},"rt":15599,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60163,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"110 AM12 PMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1291"},"rt":12975,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":73266,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"U E E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1292"},"rt":59534,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132890,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"C C C A C C 11 AMO 311 AMC C O A A C C C O 1A 11 AM10 AMZ Z 02 PMC C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1293"},"rt":21015,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154061,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"C 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1294"},"rt":68853,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223116,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O A J I U 5O O U U Z 12 PM11 AMG F 12 PM01 PM02 PM501 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1296"},"rt":9426,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":240580,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1297"},"rt":25292,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265976,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F Z F B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1298"},"rt":71354,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337507,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G F F F E E E E E F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1299"},"rt":15428,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":353311,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F F J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e129a"},"rt":36122,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389530,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"5F B B F Z Z F F Z Z Z Z J M X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e129b"},"rt":10873,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":400501,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I B B B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e129c"},"rt":10789,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411379,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B F B 12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e129d"},"rt":44907,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":456503,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"O Z Z O O X X X X X X F F F F J J J M M B B G G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e129e"},"rt":44379,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501072,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e129f"},"rt":82104,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583273,"subject":"6FM91","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,M ","hovered":"4M M 01 PM12 PM11 AMJ 01 PM02 PMX X X B B B B B 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PMM B B B I J B B J M M M M M M X X X X X C C 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b0"},"rt":42477,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62381,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"6O Z 01 PM02 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMH I O O A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b1"},"rt":7698,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70392,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"U D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b2"},"rt":9919,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":80587,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b3"},"rt":37575,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118264,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMU U U F F U U 02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b4"},"rt":86903,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205273,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z Z I 04 PMF F 03 PM04 PMH I I O O O I 06 PM04 PM01 PM02 PMO O A Z Z U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b6"},"rt":7325,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":220789,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b7"},"rt":18750,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239644,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b8"},"rt":28419,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268168,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B B X X 04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12b9"},"rt":20309,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":288584,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B B J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12ba"},"rt":47327,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":336020,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"N N X X Z N X F F F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PMX X X X X F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12bb"},"rt":6941,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343381,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM03 PMM M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12bc"},"rt":11086,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354571,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12bd"},"rt":25628,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":380307,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12be"},"rt":70146,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":450559,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M B B F E E I B B O O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12bf"},"rt":55551,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506564,"subject":"QGTVP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"O 02 PMM F X X F F E E E G G E B B B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d0"},"rt":17540,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167847,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"10 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d1"},"rt":8946,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176878,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d2"},"rt":13456,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190417,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d3"},"rt":12099,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202608,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PMU U U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d4"},"rt":113080,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315772,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F K K F F 03 PMU 03 PM08 AM001 PM12 PM01 PMZ Z O O H H H 01 PM01 PMH J H H H H H 01 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d6"},"rt":6014,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327909,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d7"},"rt":32147,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360142,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"3I B F F F B B B B B D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d8"},"rt":54573,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414849,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"I G G G X X X B F F F F E E 11 AM11 AME I 09 AM11 AM04 PM03 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12d9"},"rt":22445,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":437376,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I J J J 01 PMM 444"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12da"},"rt":48852,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486309,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X F F B 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PMF F I 10 AM11 AMJ M M B B B F F E 11 AM01 PMM X C C X X X X O C C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12db"},"rt":10288,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496684,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"12 PM12 PMB B B F B B B 01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12dc"},"rt":7406,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504174,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12dd"},"rt":13436,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":517695,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z X B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12de"},"rt":26022,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543810,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"H 01 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMX X X B I B E 11 AM12 PMF C X X G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12df"},"rt":25114,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":569015,"subject":"LOGAL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43292","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"J J X X X B B F M M M M F E 11 AME B B B B F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f0"},"rt":75985,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":879810,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,F ","hovered":"A A A Z Z A 09 AM10 AM11 AMC A A C C C A F F F F K F F F F F F F F O F F O F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f1"},"rt":14931,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":894960,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"C X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f2"},"rt":17903,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":912961,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,F ","hovered":"O C A A O O F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f3"},"rt":13614,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":926648,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"U H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f4"},"rt":15616,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":942337,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f6"},"rt":11285,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1052265,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f7"},"rt":104326,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1156662,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,O ","hovered":"C C H O O O O O C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f8"},"rt":51002,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1207888,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"I Z C G B B G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12f9"},"rt":304410,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1512372,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"M F 556I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12fa"},"rt":10758,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1523351,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12fb"},"rt":55225,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1578648,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"5O M M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12fc"},"rt":7647,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1586367,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12fd"},"rt":15597,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1602037,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,I ","hovered":"Z E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12fe"},"rt":21544,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1623651,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,G ","hovered":"B G G F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e12ff"},"rt":42595,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1666320,"subject":"QMZ24","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37962","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"I B X X 02 PMX X X K X X X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1310"},"rt":19313,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90820,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"10 AMA A I I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1311"},"rt":37052,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127972,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1312"},"rt":58076,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":186146,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C A A Z Z 09 AMO Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1313"},"rt":143762,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330009,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F E F F A C C C 08 AM08 AM09 AM11 AM12 PMH C 08 AMA 0008 AMA A 08 AMC A G K F A A C C A A C A A A Z F F F F O O O O O I H F H H H H U U K B B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1314"},"rt":191163,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521547,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F I O O O O O O I I O 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PMF I O O O O O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMO 12 PMO O Z Z F F F 01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMH 01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PMH H H U 02 PM02 PM03 PMU K X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1316"},"rt":15015,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":542968,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1317"},"rt":34979,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":578046,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I J C H C F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1318"},"rt":101807,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679955,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"8E E E X 02 PM02 PM03 PME G G E I J J E E B I X I 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMJ 10 AM12 PME F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1319"},"rt":64508,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":744802,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I J J J I 10 AM11 AM12 PMI I I 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e131a"},"rt":118398,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":863525,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B B 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMO 07 PM06 PMX 02 PM03 PM04 PMX O B B B J E E G C C 01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e131b"},"rt":14069,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":877943,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"4B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e131c"},"rt":13349,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":891391,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e131d"},"rt":44011,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":935503,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z B B B B F B B M X X X X F F 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e131e"},"rt":58712,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":994314,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"2J E F F B B M M G G G C X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e131f"},"rt":126915,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1121332,"subject":"ADRO0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"B B B B F B O O B I I J B B B M M M C C E E E E E X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1330"},"rt":40450,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62346,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"111 AMA C C A A 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1331"},"rt":7569,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70006,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"412 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1332"},"rt":11562,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81676,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"10 AM10 AMC A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1333"},"rt":10798,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92586,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"01 PM03 PM04 PMU U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1334"},"rt":39513,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132188,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U I O O 11 AMO O O G G 10 AM11 AMU U F 33A U U G U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1336"},"rt":6629,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":140633,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E C 01 PM12 PM11 AMI E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1337"},"rt":16568,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157340,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"02 PM01 PMM M C F F B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1338"},"rt":49672,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207153,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"E E F F B B F B B B F F B B B B B B G F F B B I N N B B B B M M M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1339"},"rt":5181,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":212430,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e133a"},"rt":19825,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232379,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B I B B B B F Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e133b"},"rt":3274,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235794,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e133c"},"rt":2961,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238858,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"G G E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e133d"},"rt":2904,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":241873,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e133e"},"rt":2313,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244274,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e133f"},"rt":2685,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247086,"subject":"LWUQ3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43325","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1350"},"rt":53923,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144909,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C 10 AM10 AM11 AMA A 12 PM11 AMA A A C C A A F C C C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1351"},"rt":9779,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154793,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E D D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1352"},"rt":29629,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184514,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1353"},"rt":9303,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193934,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"04 PMH 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1354"},"rt":12473,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206524,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O O 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1356"},"rt":23913,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":236755,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM01 PM12 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM10 AME E E E G F F 10 AMO O G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1357"},"rt":28792,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265648,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"J I B B B O O O O X 02 PM01 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1358"},"rt":65211,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330959,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F B G F X X X G O O F 10 AMB B 11 AMB B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1359"},"rt":47721,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":379032,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B J J J I E E E F F I I B 11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AME E E F F B B J I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e135a"},"rt":16058,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395402,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e135b"},"rt":14367,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409887,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"F 02 PM01 PM12 PMM M L L 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e135c"},"rt":6636,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416610,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"G C F F E F F F F G G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e135d"},"rt":13920,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":430636,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O C Z N N N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e135e"},"rt":13890,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444637,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"03 PMX X X 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e135f"},"rt":12450,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457226,"subject":"D6P9K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43079","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1370"},"rt":28057,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":116795,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AM12509 AM008 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1371"},"rt":38878,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155745,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"03 PM04 PMD D D E E E 04 PME E 04 PME E D D E E E E E E E J D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1372"},"rt":142653,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298472,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ","hovered":"B 05 PM05 PMD E E U A C C D D C C 03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMZ Z 10 AM04 PM02 PMB 02 PM11 AM04 PM04 PMZ D A Z 10 AMC C C C B B B D D K 03 PM02 PMC A B B 05 PM03 PM02 PMD D G G 04 PMB B B G G D E E D D K K E E 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMC C C D E D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1373"},"rt":63053,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361751,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"4I 04 PMU U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1374"},"rt":26670,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388649,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"12 PM01 PMI I O A I Z Z 12 PMA A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1376"},"rt":5642,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":402477,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1377"},"rt":22761,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425311,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C F F B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1378"},"rt":45066,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470447,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"G G B I J J J J J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1379"},"rt":25307,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":495825,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e137a"},"rt":17565,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":513460,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"F F I J J J J I I J J I I J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e137b"},"rt":10983,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524515,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C I 01 PM12 PMM B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e137c"},"rt":9788,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534374,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O O B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e137d"},"rt":23749,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":558195,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"C N Z F Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e137e"},"rt":46226,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":604528,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"02 PMM B X F 10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e137f"},"rt":27396,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":631998,"subject":"J3FYJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36602","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"O 02 PMX X X X X X F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1390"},"rt":30052,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":87925,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C 09 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM09 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1391"},"rt":8416,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96472,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"K D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1392"},"rt":22905,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119498,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C A A C 312 PM01 PMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1393"},"rt":44344,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163946,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM03 PM04 PMA Z U U 4U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1394"},"rt":19255,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183352,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"U E E E D 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1396"},"rt":7912,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":196412,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"08 AM008 AM08 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1397"},"rt":28009,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224617,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.8333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":10,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,D ,F ,I ,J ,M ,N ,O ,Z ,X ","hovered":"I J F J F F B M M X X O Z N D N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1398"},"rt":11444,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236173,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"6E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1399"},"rt":8753,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":245046,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e139a"},"rt":13871,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259029,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B B X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e139b"},"rt":8225,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267366,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"10 AM01 PM12 PMB B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e139c"},"rt":8051,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":275521,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B B B F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e139d"},"rt":23407,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299035,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"J M Z F B B B B O O O X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e139e"},"rt":11901,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311060,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"4M 03 PM03 PM03 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e139f"},"rt":8075,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319250,"subject":"NHP4G","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40699","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,G ","hovered":"5G G G C C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b0"},"rt":19500,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83690,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b1"},"rt":22154,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106012,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b2"},"rt":25429,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131544,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,U ,B ","hovered":"A U B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b3"},"rt":13045,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144679,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b4"},"rt":9540,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154410,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,K ","hovered":"O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b6"},"rt":15443,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":177936,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b7"},"rt":16197,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194307,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b8"},"rt":39522,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233949,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ,M ","hovered":"M G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13b9"},"rt":19486,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253535,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13ba"},"rt":28713,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":282370,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13bb"},"rt":15731,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298192,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13bc"},"rt":8376,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306668,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13bd"},"rt":19601,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":326364,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13be"},"rt":13324,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339784,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13bf"},"rt":23550,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363424,"subject":"QAU26","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41933","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d0"},"rt":25008,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68116,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AM11 AMA A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d1"},"rt":20292,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88658,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H D D E D E E 04 PM05 PMG C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d2"},"rt":37349,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126632,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"H C A C A A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d3"},"rt":47420,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174163,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"104 PMD D E E 04 PME E E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d4"},"rt":21984,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196327,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"J I O O Z 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d6"},"rt":16081,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":218651,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d7"},"rt":28723,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247487,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"4I B 06 PMF B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d8"},"rt":28059,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":275662,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,J ,N ","hovered":"J J J J N D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13d9"},"rt":16051,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":291843,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,I ","hovered":"4I F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13da"},"rt":7246,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299219,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13db"},"rt":21620,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321197,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"501 PM01 PM12 PMB B F B B F B 12 PM12 PM12 PMB B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13dc"},"rt":5042,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326342,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13dd"},"rt":26162,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352610,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,N ","hovered":"Z Z Z N N N D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13de"},"rt":13990,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366718,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13df"},"rt":18334,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385160,"subject":"0S724","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42706","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"11 AM10 AM09 AMX X K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f0"},"rt":20552,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107887,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"109 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f1"},"rt":18042,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126046,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"08 AMA A D J J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f2"},"rt":8551,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134716,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f3"},"rt":16185,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151051,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM03 PM04 PME E 04 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f4"},"rt":26670,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177851,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"C A C 1A A 03 PM04 PM02 PM01 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f6"},"rt":7216,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":192701,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"12 PME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f7"},"rt":14030,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206846,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f8"},"rt":37568,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244521,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.41666666666666663,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":5,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ,I ,J ,N ","hovered":"E G E E J J J I H Z Z X X N D N O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13f9"},"rt":49531,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":294185,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,M ","hovered":"J G G J I I I I B M M O O 12 PMM M M M O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13fa"},"rt":19263,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313568,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"2F J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13fb"},"rt":9117,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322825,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PMB B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13fc"},"rt":10045,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332992,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13fd"},"rt":39735,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":372863,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z F F B B B X X X X X B B B X F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13fe"},"rt":40136,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413117,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B O B 12 PM12 PMM M M M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e13ff"},"rt":48719,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461947,"subject":"2W0WT","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42012","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,E ","hovered":"10 AM02 PM02 PMX X X C C C E E H B B J B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1410"},"rt":2568,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":20076,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1411"},"rt":1156,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":21339,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1412"},"rt":1048,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":22471,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1413"},"rt":1708,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":24262,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1414"},"rt":1017,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":25384,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1416"},"rt":1786,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":27848,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1417"},"rt":1780,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":29722,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"4F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1418"},"rt":1198,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":31074,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"B B F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1419"},"rt":2579,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":33756,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"4F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e141a"},"rt":1949,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":35794,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e141b"},"rt":1241,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":37120,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e141c"},"rt":1873,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":39073,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e141d"},"rt":1182,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":40342,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e141e"},"rt":1319,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41752,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e141f"},"rt":1190,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43021,"subject":"ZDQ5M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1430"},"rt":16673,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":74570,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A Z A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1431"},"rt":9909,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84568,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1432"},"rt":34394,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119050,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"O C C A A C C A Z Z C C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1433"},"rt":11953,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131203,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"E K K K U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1434"},"rt":103548,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234843,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I O I O K K K H O O O F F J 11 AMJ O F F U U I G G I U U H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1436"},"rt":8243,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":247710,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1437"},"rt":14264,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262084,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B B F B B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1438"},"rt":34330,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296511,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F B B I E 5X 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1439"},"rt":12661,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309267,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e143a"},"rt":30603,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339979,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F Z X I X X O B M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e143b"},"rt":7576,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347636,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F F B B B F B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e143c"},"rt":3859,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351580,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e143d"},"rt":26221,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377884,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z X X X Z G E E Z Z Z F F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e143e"},"rt":29408,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407381,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e143f"},"rt":16458,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423924,"subject":"NU6LU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41860","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"02 PMX X F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1450"},"rt":57919,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113435,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1451"},"rt":72774,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":186321,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"E D K K K K 03 PMK K K K C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1452"},"rt":31326,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217941,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"6A C C C 10 AMA Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1453"},"rt":12661,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230706,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1454"},"rt":70167,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300982,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I I I O O A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1456"},"rt":9375,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":315861,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"4E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1457"},"rt":51390,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367355,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ,O ","hovered":"B B B F F B F B B O N N D D N O O X X X O H O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1458"},"rt":49677,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417134,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"H H O X X B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1459"},"rt":73774,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":491017,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"G J I J J J B B M B I B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e145a"},"rt":9329,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500627,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e145b"},"rt":9708,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510438,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"F M M M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e145c"},"rt":13509,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524049,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F B F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e145d"},"rt":22901,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":547046,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"N B B F F F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e145e"},"rt":18404,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565633,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F B B B F F X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e145f"},"rt":45024,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":610761,"subject":"31386","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30237","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,X ","hovered":"X X X X X X X J X X C P K O K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1470"},"rt":22967,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92461,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AM09 AMC 09 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1471"},"rt":17528,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":110096,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"D J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1472"},"rt":53794,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164163,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C B B C U B B X X C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1473"},"rt":45702,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209961,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"O K K O K K A E E U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1474"},"rt":29232,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239335,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"I I K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1476"},"rt":27485,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":274373,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"J E G E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1477"},"rt":29288,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303769,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,H ","hovered":"11 AM11 AMC H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1478"},"rt":71498,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375372,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"J E L M B B F B B B F F L K X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1479"},"rt":12069,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387793,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J J J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e147a"},"rt":13978,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401882,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e147b"},"rt":13974,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415955,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"2B B F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e147c"},"rt":13718,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":429770,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e147d"},"rt":21316,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":451190,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"Z O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e147e"},"rt":90579,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541885,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"H O 03 PMG G 05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e147f"},"rt":29880,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572121,"subject":"BCPEC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37206","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"X F F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1490"},"rt":18152,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155150,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"101 PM12 PM11 AMA A A A O O 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1491"},"rt":11657,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166979,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"03 PM03 PMG B D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1492"},"rt":11577,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178675,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C 10 AM11 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1493"},"rt":40428,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219238,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"K K K U U U F F O A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1494"},"rt":98432,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317838,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I 03 PMU 03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1496"},"rt":7717,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":333253,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"01 PMB G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1497"},"rt":19946,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353346,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1498"},"rt":49191,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402673,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1499"},"rt":11885,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414692,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I J J J 3I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e149a"},"rt":42849,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457677,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F Z F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e149b"},"rt":8945,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466768,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"4M 03 PM02 PM01 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e149c"},"rt":6084,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472988,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e149d"},"rt":17939,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":491060,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z F F Z Z X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e149e"},"rt":26341,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517620,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B 04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e149f"},"rt":35210,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553047,"subject":"6Q1UC","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36989","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"302 PM01 PM03 PMF 02 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b0"},"rt":18589,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68472,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z Z 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b1"},"rt":22053,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90620,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"12 PM03 PM03 PME E E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b2"},"rt":16920,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107644,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C 10 AM10 AMC Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b3"},"rt":56879,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164662,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"2A 04 PMC C A A A A Z Z Z Z F O O I I U K K 3U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b4"},"rt":262836,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427605,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I O O I O O Z Z I O O U A C C A Z Z Z Z F F O O O H H H H H U U U B H H U K K K K U U J H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b6"},"rt":9702,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":445018,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b7"},"rt":27115,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472221,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"G E C C F B B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b8"},"rt":63314,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535637,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L L F F E J J I I B O X I B F B X X J I I M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14b9"},"rt":43954,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":579884,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F M M J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14ba"},"rt":96246,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":676227,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B B 12 PMF B B B B F J J J M M F F F M F B M M Z X Z M X O O 02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14bb"},"rt":9039,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":685549,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB B F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14bc"},"rt":5768,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":691406,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14bd"},"rt":27705,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":719204,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"03 PM03 PMZ Z H O 04 PM03 PMF F F 02 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14be"},"rt":29428,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":749170,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMB B 12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14bf"},"rt":160047,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":909306,"subject":"OU3SL","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32414","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"X X X X X 03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMX X M M 11 AM11 AM10 AMI J J E E 11 AME 12 PMB B F 02 PM01 PMM 01 PM01 PMG G X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d0"},"rt":30476,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":95765,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"111 AM11 AMA A 11 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d1"},"rt":8469,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":104341,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d2"},"rt":19427,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124077,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C A Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d3"},"rt":57751,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182050,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A C U F F F 12 PMF 01 PMO Z Z Z Z H H I I I O O C C C 08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PMK U U U F F F F 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d4"},"rt":53096,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235438,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I I O O 03 PMU 02 PM02 PM01 PMH E I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d6"},"rt":9470,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":249789,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"4I E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d7"},"rt":18708,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268742,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PMM 6F B B B F F F 12 PM12 PMF Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d8"},"rt":26611,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295474,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14d9"},"rt":24533,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":320145,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"8J J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14da"},"rt":32443,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352713,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B B B O Z X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14db"},"rt":15713,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368534,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"02 PM03 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14dc"},"rt":6744,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375652,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B 12 PM12 PM6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14dd"},"rt":44229,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":419988,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"H 04 PM04 PMO 03 PM04 PMO O X X X O C C 01 PMG G G J J M M M F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14de"},"rt":35644,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":455911,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"08 PM08 PM07 PMO O O X X C C C C M M M M G B B F B 12 PM12 PMF B B 12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14df"},"rt":58962,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515031,"subject":"ZRRZW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M M M M M M B B B B F F 11 AM11 AMF G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f0"},"rt":14559,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55869,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"4A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f1"},"rt":12835,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68779,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"Z D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f2"},"rt":33377,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102237,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f3"},"rt":29570,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131873,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"01 PM02 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMU U U U F Z Z Z Z A Z 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f4"},"rt":39407,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171349,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A U G I 12 PM12 PM01 PM03 PMU U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f6"},"rt":9540,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":185976,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f7"},"rt":19028,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205136,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"6F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f8"},"rt":15241,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":220510,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14f9"},"rt":10771,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231385,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"2J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14fa"},"rt":12455,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243954,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"M F F F X X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14fb"},"rt":13925,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258020,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"08 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PMF B B B B B I B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14fc"},"rt":8346,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266529,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14fd"},"rt":21413,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":288068,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"Z Z Z 04 PM03 PM02 PMX X X 01 PMM M 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14fe"},"rt":21487,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":309716,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"03 PM03 PMO X M M B B B B F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e14ff"},"rt":18917,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328748,"subject":"GNP7O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35451","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"02 PM01 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1510"},"rt":24460,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62632,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"44C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1511"},"rt":7515,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70240,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E G G E K 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1512"},"rt":13521,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83859,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"4C C A A A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1513"},"rt":24502,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108448,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"5Z K K U U U H J H H F Z Z A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1514"},"rt":23075,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131641,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"A C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1516"},"rt":5215,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":141747,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1517"},"rt":13969,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155817,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"E G L F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1518"},"rt":20651,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176600,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E G G G B B B F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1519"},"rt":34004,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":210700,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"I I J J I J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e151a"},"rt":14463,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225250,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"5G F J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e151b"},"rt":4434,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229785,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M M B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e151c"},"rt":2867,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232739,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e151d"},"rt":23370,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256200,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B B H H Z Z Z Z Z Z Z O X X C C G B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e151e"},"rt":22647,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278933,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F 03 PM03 PMX X C B B M M M J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e151f"},"rt":27670,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306692,"subject":"VWB05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42846\\","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"E G G C C G G G B F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1530"},"rt":16337,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":51418,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1531"},"rt":8949,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60472,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1532"},"rt":52616,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113198,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"C C C A B U A C C C C X X F F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1533"},"rt":17093,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130398,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ","hovered":"E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1534"},"rt":16214,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146718,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I I H I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1536"},"rt":11851,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":163560,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1537"},"rt":10101,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173767,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,I ","hovered":"I I B I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1538"},"rt":25730,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199605,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"G B B X O B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1539"},"rt":8553,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":208262,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e153a"},"rt":5582,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213953,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e153b"},"rt":8549,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":222611,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M 12 PM11 AMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e153c"},"rt":4441,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227155,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e153d"},"rt":31420,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":258678,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z I I I B O X X B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e153e"},"rt":19659,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278440,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e153f"},"rt":26791,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305336,"subject":"6B6X6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41516","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"A F X F F C C G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1550"},"rt":25322,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":648329,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"10 AMZ A A C Z Z Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1551"},"rt":12705,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661195,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E 04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1552"},"rt":11879,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":673324,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"E A C C 11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1553"},"rt":57305,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":730811,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"08 AM09 AM03 PM02 PMC Z A A Z Z Z F F F O O O O O I O O 11 AMI I H H I I O U U U U U U U O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1554"},"rt":46045,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":777415,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"I I O O U K K H I O O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1556"},"rt":6454,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":791687,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1557"},"rt":13826,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":805698,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1558"},"rt":16827,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":822677,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G C G B B B B E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1559"},"rt":11076,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":833948,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"4B J I 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e155a"},"rt":21046,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":855163,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B B F F 12 PM12 PMB B F F I B B M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e155b"},"rt":5657,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":860989,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e155c"},"rt":4674,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":865943,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e155d"},"rt":19251,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":885397,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"5Z 04 PMO O O X X M M M B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e155e"},"rt":15694,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":901252,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M X X B B C X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e155f"},"rt":29898,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":931683,"subject":"D4XSD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40150","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PMX B B F F F B B B I E E F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1570"},"rt":27700,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48206,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1571"},"rt":14206,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":63205,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"3J D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1572"},"rt":45467,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108853,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"U C A B A C A Z Z Z B B Z C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1573"},"rt":30626,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":139616,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PME E E 04 PME E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1574"},"rt":185075,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324849,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,I ","hovered":"C Z Z O Z G G K H O E E H C Z Z A Z Z Z A A 11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMO O I K H H H 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1576"},"rt":10624,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":340723,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"4E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1577"},"rt":10228,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351065,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1578"},"rt":67150,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418420,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,N ","hovered":"X 04 PMZ O O O O O O H H O X 04 PMZ N D Z Z Z Z H X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1579"},"rt":18955,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":437835,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e157a"},"rt":70442,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":508395,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMZ Z Z O B B F B B O F E A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e157b"},"rt":8490,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517869,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e157c"},"rt":8161,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":526445,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e157d"},"rt":42943,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":569509,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"H Z Z Z F B B B B F E G C E A A G G C C H H H B O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e157e"},"rt":35960,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":605597,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ,X ","hovered":"03 PMX O B B F F E G G C C H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e157f"},"rt":33595,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":639319,"subject":"Z39WH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28217","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"03 PM02 PMX X X 02 PM02 PMX X X F F B B O O B B G J M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1590"},"rt":2972,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":15930,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1591"},"rt":4688,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":20712,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H H H E K E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1592"},"rt":4611,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":25403,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1593"},"rt":9227,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34718,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"A C A A C C A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1594"},"rt":18474,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53281,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,U ","hovered":"3C A A A A A O F F F F F U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1596"},"rt":3805,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":58487,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"4E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1597"},"rt":8202,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66771,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"5I I F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1598"},"rt":15456,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82314,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"I I J J 4E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1599"},"rt":14246,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":96647,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"F I I I 3I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e159a"},"rt":8220,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":104959,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"4F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e159b"},"rt":4462,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109497,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e159c"},"rt":4489,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114073,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"4B 3B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e159d"},"rt":8177,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":122329,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F B B F F F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e159e"},"rt":8231,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130644,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F X B B B B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e159f"},"rt":5284,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136016,"subject":"KWP9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42132","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b0"},"rt":45958,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130000,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"11 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b1"},"rt":27839,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157931,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"E D E E 04 PMC C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b2"},"rt":95497,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253511,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C 10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b3"},"rt":15067,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268810,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM03 PM04 PMU U U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b4"},"rt":87367,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356258,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I Z F H H J H H 01 PMU U H H J J J F F U U 02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMH O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b6"},"rt":10418,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":378048,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G E 4G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b7"},"rt":24323,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402457,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"4B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b8"},"rt":50727,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":453275,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"7B B E J M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15b9"},"rt":19414,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":472772,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15ba"},"rt":34743,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":507599,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"5F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PMX B B B 12 PMB B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15bb"},"rt":11152,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":518837,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"4I B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15bc"},"rt":9020,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528005,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"3J B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15bd"},"rt":42952,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":571107,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"O X H H Z X 02 PM01 PMC O B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15be"},"rt":18538,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":589794,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"J M M B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15bf"},"rt":55082,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":645024,"subject":"XLH9B","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M B B B B F 12 PMB M M E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d0"},"rt":79335,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145525,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"03 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMC C C Z 02 PM02 PMX X X X D O A A A C C Z C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d1"},"rt":15138,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161096,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E 5K E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d2"},"rt":8667,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169911,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d3"},"rt":66999,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237029,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"E A U U F F F F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d4"},"rt":45793,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283229,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"3K H I O O U U U U 12 PM12 PMI O O 12 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d6"},"rt":7767,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":296525,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d7"},"rt":16199,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312848,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"5I B F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d8"},"rt":26252,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339362,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B F E O O O B X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15d9"},"rt":19947,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359462,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15da"},"rt":47402,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406982,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"6B B B B F B B 12 PM12 PMX E E X X C J G G O 02 PMX O B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15db"},"rt":8158,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415253,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15dc"},"rt":5754,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":421157,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15dd"},"rt":40314,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":461606,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z O X X X C G G F B B M M J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15de"},"rt":24983,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486718,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M J B B B B B F B B B B A C X X M M X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15df"},"rt":35414,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":522243,"subject":"KPQ31","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38352","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"B B M M M M F E E 11 AM12 PM01 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f0"},"rt":15900,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43021,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C A A C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f1"},"rt":10660,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53778,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f2"},"rt":16454,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70356,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f3"},"rt":57847,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128313,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"3C A A E E E U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f4"},"rt":4696,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133114,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"4C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f6"},"rt":6134,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":145491,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"1G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f7"},"rt":2566,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148165,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f8"},"rt":3060,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151676,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"G G A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15f9"},"rt":2449,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":154235,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ","hovered":"L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15fa"},"rt":2220,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156555,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P ","hovered":"P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15fb"},"rt":4424,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161087,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15fc"},"rt":1900,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163092,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15fd"},"rt":2655,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":165847,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15fe"},"rt":2897,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168870,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e15ff"},"rt":2138,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171106,"subject":"1YLQF","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41643","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1610"},"rt":17385,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":50202,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"X 02 PMF Z A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1611"},"rt":6444,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":56758,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1612"},"rt":19372,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76249,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"H 02 PMF A A C A O O A A A C C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1613"},"rt":37845,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114209,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"01 PMB B 04 PM04 PME E E C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1614"},"rt":30206,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144532,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"I O O O O O O O O O O O O O I 08 AMF Z Z O O O I O Z Z F 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1616"},"rt":9447,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":158923,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1617"},"rt":12382,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171411,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1618"},"rt":30720,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202245,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"N B B B B B B B B B X X X 03 PM02 PMX 03 PM4J B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1619"},"rt":8226,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":210590,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"07 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e161a"},"rt":14466,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225182,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F 12 PM11 AM11 AMF F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e161b"},"rt":12556,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237861,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"02 PM11 AM01 PM02 PM12 PMM 01 PM01 PM2M L 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e161c"},"rt":9768,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247749,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,G ","hovered":"G O 01 PMG G G F F F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e161d"},"rt":10617,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":267901,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F F E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e161e"},"rt":9228,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277254,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"11 AM01 PM01 PM01 PMX X 03 PMM 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e161f"},"rt":20468,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297837,"subject":"DJ72H","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33635","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"10 AM01 PM02 PM02 PMX 02 PMX 02 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1630"},"rt":23275,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84193,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A 04 PM12 PMC 11 AM11 AMI O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1631"},"rt":34165,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118461,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A D J D D J E E 04 PME E E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1632"},"rt":113599,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232158,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ,J ,H ,F ,K ,D ,U ,E ,G ,B ,Z ","hovered":"5A A C 10 AMC C C C C C Z Z Z 12 PM01 PMH E E 12 PMC C 10 AMC 10 AM11 AMZ O O F U U K H H H J X D D D E G G B B F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1633"},"rt":55311,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287768,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"11 AM12 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMK U X X X 09 AM09 AMC C 08 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM08 AM04 PM04 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1634"},"rt":140521,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428391,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I O O O 12 PM12 PM06 PM07 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMO O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM03 PMU U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1636"},"rt":15702,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":450164,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1637"},"rt":55044,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":505305,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B Z Z Z N N D N 02 PM01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1638"},"rt":133843,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":639247,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B B B F E I E X X 02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM07 PMZ X 02 PMX X X X 02 PM02 PMX J 11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX X 03 PM04 PM03 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PMX B B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1639"},"rt":37490,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":677043,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B B J I 10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e163a"},"rt":154218,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":831362,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B F F B B 12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PMM M J I B I I J J I I 10 AMJ M M J 12 PMI 12 PM12 PMB B F 03 PM04 PM04 PMB 04 PMB M M M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e163b"},"rt":6785,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":838451,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"112 PM12 PMB B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e163c"},"rt":12765,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":851318,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B F 01 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e163d"},"rt":42392,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":893810,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z Z 04 PMF F F X B B B F B 12 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMO O O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e163e"},"rt":103722,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":997642,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM02 PMB J M M X 02 PMX B O B 12 PM12 PMB B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e163f"},"rt":92417,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1090355,"subject":"Z6CB2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38605","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"01 PM02 PMF F E E E E F 02 PMF F Z E G 05 PM05 PMF 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1650"},"rt":29622,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98503,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"1A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1651"},"rt":27171,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125958,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B D E E E D D D D E E D D D E 04 PM04 PMG G 04 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1652"},"rt":59682,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185915,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C C A U B 01 PM10 AM03 PM04 PM03 PMC C C A U U B 10 AM10 AM10 AMC C C A Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1653"},"rt":17447,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203666,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"Z 02 PM03 PM04 PME E D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1654"},"rt":28174,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232123,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"09 AM10 AM01 PM12 PM11 AMZ J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1656"},"rt":12319,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256032,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"J E E G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1657"},"rt":30408,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286759,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C F B B B B F F F F B F B B X O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1658"},"rt":68750,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":355785,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L F F I I B B F B B B B F F F F B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1659"},"rt":20095,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":376210,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"A A 03 PM02 PM01 PMJ I I B B 3I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e165a"},"rt":10407,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386886,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"F 04 PMZ Z Z 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e165b"},"rt":17341,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":404519,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M 02 PM01 PM12 PMB B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e165c"},"rt":9081,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413876,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e165d"},"rt":33423,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":447565,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"02 PMN Z F F B B F F X X O O C C G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e165e"},"rt":20958,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468840,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PMC B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e165f"},"rt":68569,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":537683,"subject":"HNM67","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"33748","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"04 PM05 PM06 PM05 PM02 PMM B F F O O X B E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1670"},"rt":12840,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71224,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1671"},"rt":6441,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":77768,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"02 PM01 PME 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1672"},"rt":9219,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":87090,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1673"},"rt":128,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":87321,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1674"},"rt":74565,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161988,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I O O 12 PMU U K 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1676"},"rt":8728,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":179467,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"X 6E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1677"},"rt":24078,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203645,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1678"},"rt":26379,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230120,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"6B E E E F J J I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1679"},"rt":13410,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243638,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J I J J 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e167a"},"rt":50947,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294683,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F I B F I I I J J I F I I J J B B 4B J F F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMX C E B F B B M C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e167b"},"rt":9149,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303941,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e167c"},"rt":9007,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313049,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e167d"},"rt":21760,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":334900,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"503 PMF F E E G C C B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e167e"},"rt":47652,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":382671,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X O F B M M M O O O 03 PMI B 11 AM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e167f"},"rt":38508,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":421292,"subject":"CNMNJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37105","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"B 02 PMM M 01 PM01 PM02 PMI I E E F F B B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1690"},"rt":15684,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":50508,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"775A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1691"},"rt":7234,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":57881,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F U U K E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1692"},"rt":16614,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":74612,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"U U Z A 3C Z Z A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1693"},"rt":34900,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109639,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"3C 03 PM03 PME E E E E H H F 01 PM04 PM01 PM12 PMZ Z F K K U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1694"},"rt":23760,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133518,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"H I I I 12 PM12 PMK K O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1696"},"rt":5439,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":141640,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"M M E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1697"},"rt":13519,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155365,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1698"},"rt":16582,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172077,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"F B J J J J J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1699"},"rt":25279,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":197467,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"2J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e169a"},"rt":14082,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211664,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F B B F F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e169b"},"rt":7846,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219634,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J M M M M B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e169c"},"rt":5114,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224866,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e169d"},"rt":29073,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":254065,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,Z ","hovered":"Z N D D N C C L L C C C C O H H Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e169e"},"rt":9269,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263451,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B O O O B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e169f"},"rt":11760,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":275322,"subject":"MJ2W9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"28943","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"02 PMF F F B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b0"},"rt":31267,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84617,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"12 PM11 AM10 AMO O A A A 2C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b1"},"rt":43834,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128551,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O F E E D E E E E E 12 PMK D X U U G D D D D D X X K K K K K K D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b2"},"rt":15212,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":143863,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C C C 11 AMA C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b3"},"rt":9661,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153618,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMH Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b4"},"rt":49734,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203449,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"K I 03 PM03 PMU U U U I F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b6"},"rt":13083,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":220048,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b7"},"rt":22674,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242814,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"6C C H H C B B B B B B B F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b8"},"rt":50575,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293481,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"G L L X X 03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMX E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16b9"},"rt":21950,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":315525,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F J J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16ba"},"rt":16834,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332462,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H E 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16bb"},"rt":5756,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338311,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16bc"},"rt":9638,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348051,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"J X X M F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16bd"},"rt":31119,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":379269,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,G ,O ","hovered":"N N M N Z Z Z O O C C G Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16be"},"rt":11843,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391208,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F F X 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16bf"},"rt":25235,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416544,"subject":"F37T6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42936","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"44N N X J X X X X G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d0"},"rt":106773,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160899,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA 12 PM11 AM11 AMA Z Z 12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AMC C C C A A 01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d1"},"rt":9025,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":170433,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"7O E E E C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d2"},"rt":17946,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188715,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C A Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d3"},"rt":91286,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280116,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMU U 02 PMK F F F H K K O O O O O O O H H H J 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d4"},"rt":114212,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395144,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I 03 PMU F F F F F F F Z Z O O O A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d6"},"rt":20880,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":418467,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"G E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d7"},"rt":14269,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432901,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d8"},"rt":35096,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468115,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"8G G E X X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16d9"},"rt":23268,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":491689,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I I I B I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16da"},"rt":72630,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564576,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"N L F F 04 PM04 PMX X O B B F X X X F F F G G G E E E B B M M 01 PMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16db"},"rt":11533,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":576396,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"O M M B B M M M M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16dc"},"rt":6317,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":582996,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"8G B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16dd"},"rt":68315,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":651411,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"X X X X F F 05 PMF O C 12 PM12 PM12 PM04 PM04 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMM O O O O 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16de"},"rt":54719,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":706807,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMB 11 AM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16df"},"rt":81561,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":788475,"subject":"KZOE9","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43245","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F 05 PM03 PM02 PMC C C 02 PM01 PM01 PM01 PMM M 12 PM12 PM12 PMF B E E E E 11 AMC C M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f0"},"rt":14164,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":75527,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A C 3A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f1"},"rt":7469,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83100,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f2"},"rt":23814,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107012,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"I O O C C C C A Z Z Z 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f3"},"rt":29239,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136341,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U K K K U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f4"},"rt":46607,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183131,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"O O I I I O O I I 01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMU U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f6"},"rt":5210,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":195878,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"6E G G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f7"},"rt":9482,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205456,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"7E G H F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f8"},"rt":24074,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229617,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E B B B I J J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16f9"},"rt":15398,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":245102,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"6F B I J J I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16fa"},"rt":14788,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259974,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"C F F B B 12 PMB B B B F 04 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16fb"},"rt":8604,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268686,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"D N X B B B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16fc"},"rt":3467,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272241,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"5B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16fd"},"rt":12337,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":284669,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"F H Z Z X X X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16fe"},"rt":12248,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297010,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X X X B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e16ff"},"rt":16421,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313524,"subject":"9OEG6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43255","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"4I 02 PM03 PMF 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1710"},"rt":30519,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98473,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1711"},"rt":5782,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":104395,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"10E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1712"},"rt":15959,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120504,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"12 PM12 PMC Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1713"},"rt":59443,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":180081,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"E E E E E E E U U F U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1714"},"rt":120539,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300798,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I O O F F I I I I K U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1716"},"rt":10674,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":326573,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E 5G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1717"},"rt":25651,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352361,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B F F F F B B B C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1718"},"rt":14693,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367216,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"B X X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1719"},"rt":19670,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387037,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e171a"},"rt":32642,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419818,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B F Z Z F Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e171b"},"rt":11226,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431201,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e171c"},"rt":9724,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441062,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e171d"},"rt":20636,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":461844,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,X ","hovered":"Z Z H G E C Z Z X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e171e"},"rt":32203,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":494209,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O O O B B O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e171f"},"rt":57651,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":551995,"subject":"C8QAW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42340","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"J J X X M M X X X X O B F F G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1730"},"rt":11518,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":63890,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1731"},"rt":12640,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76707,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"11 AMD D J E E E E J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1732"},"rt":101514,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178395,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C C A A C A F A F F F G G A F F A F F F F H K K H H F F 11 AMA C A Z Z Z 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1733"},"rt":45573,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224544,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM04 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMU 03 PM02 PMB B U 01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1734"},"rt":69405,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294120,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"5I E E H F K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1736"},"rt":7341,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":305817,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1737"},"rt":23312,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303293,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"H H C C C B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1738"},"rt":47043,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350509,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,I ","hovered":"E E 4I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1739"},"rt":13470,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":364143,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"3B J J I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e173a"},"rt":21648,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385949,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F Z B B 04 PM02 PMX 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e173b"},"rt":10038,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396168,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"11 AM01 PM12 PMM B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e173c"},"rt":10322,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406660,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B B M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e173d"},"rt":92279,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":499103,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"2Z Z 04 PM03 PMO O X X X X X X X X X X O O O O M M M M 05 PMO X M M M 01 PM01 PMM M M 11 AMM M M M E E E C Z Z 10 AM10 AMI I 01 PM12 PMM F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e173e"},"rt":23124,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":522830,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"211 AM12 PM12 PMB 01 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM10 AMJ I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e173f"},"rt":79828,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":602838,"subject":"2MMPP","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30903","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"X A F Z F F F F A A A G G G G A E G 01 PMG E 11 AMM M X C J I 12 PMA A G G 01 PMM M 12 PMB B B B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1750"},"rt":9127,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66119,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1751"},"rt":5086,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71546,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1752"},"rt":12605,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84260,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1753"},"rt":8516,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92866,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1754"},"rt":39896,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132851,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1756"},"rt":11688,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":148508,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"E G Z O O X X K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1757"},"rt":27693,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176296,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1758"},"rt":23242,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199628,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1759"},"rt":11321,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":211042,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e175a"},"rt":16912,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228043,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e175b"},"rt":6371,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234507,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e175c"},"rt":11760,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246356,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e175d"},"rt":38354,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":284800,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"G G H H O X X X X X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e175e"},"rt":4981,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289873,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e175f"},"rt":32415,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322377,"subject":"8NURS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39717","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"X F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1770"},"rt":9278,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":45798,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1771"},"rt":14559,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60457,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"33G G G D J J E E D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1772"},"rt":16678,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":77238,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"87Z C C C C A A Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1773"},"rt":8914,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86245,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z E U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1774"},"rt":20547,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106886,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"5F O F F F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1776"},"rt":10157,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":119080,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1777"},"rt":17061,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136238,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"8F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1778"},"rt":22146,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158494,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1779"},"rt":15154,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":173745,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e177a"},"rt":7598,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181443,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e177b"},"rt":10197,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":191737,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB F F B B B I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e177c"},"rt":15543,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207375,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e177d"},"rt":16169,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":223647,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,X ","hovered":"O Z X X X X B E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e177e"},"rt":11973,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235722,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,M ","hovered":"M M M M M B F G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e177f"},"rt":17938,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253758,"subject":"KTUY1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36587","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PMX X G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1790"},"rt":17823,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":75869,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1791"},"rt":13142,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89115,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1792"},"rt":18600,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107815,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1793"},"rt":10281,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118216,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"E K H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1794"},"rt":9045,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127365,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1796"},"rt":25047,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":156462,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"B 10 AM11 AM02 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM10 AMC G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1797"},"rt":9604,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166220,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1798"},"rt":38517,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204880,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1799"},"rt":14931,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":219914,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e179a"},"rt":7633,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227647,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,E ","hovered":"E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e179b"},"rt":6214,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234132,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e179c"},"rt":7601,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241832,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ,P ","hovered":"G P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e179d"},"rt":7696,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":249647,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"12 PM01 PMF F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e179e"},"rt":5448,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255199,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e179f"},"rt":6346,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261684,"subject":"R1K0J","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43283","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b0"},"rt":76363,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117282,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"110 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b1"},"rt":10658,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128235,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b2"},"rt":13807,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142160,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b3"},"rt":11212,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153476,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b4"},"rt":37111,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190705,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O O O O I 11 AM11 AMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b6"},"rt":4520,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":198468,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b7"},"rt":11458,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210068,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b8"},"rt":15641,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225847,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17b9"},"rt":7426,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233384,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17ba"},"rt":30121,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263649,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B F M M M M F B B 12 PMX M M F F F B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17bb"},"rt":9565,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273371,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M M M B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17bc"},"rt":8194,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281708,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17bd"},"rt":19514,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":301357,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z O X X X C G M M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17be"},"rt":12072,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313546,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX M M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17bf"},"rt":15245,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328937,"subject":"47G4D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M B B F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d0"},"rt":19237,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86448,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"O A A A A C 5A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d1"},"rt":11491,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98050,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A O I I D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d2"},"rt":36183,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134337,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C A A C C A A A Z Z C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d3"},"rt":45106,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179584,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A A U U K K Z Z F O O O O O U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d4"},"rt":61658,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241337,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H I O O O O O I I I O K K I I F F F H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d6"},"rt":10519,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":260899,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d7"},"rt":15627,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276633,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C H F F Z F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d8"},"rt":46052,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322804,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C F B B B B F F E E E G X X X F I B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17d9"},"rt":34423,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":357327,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17da"},"rt":48898,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406336,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"C F F Z Z F F B O O I O C C C X M M M X X M M J M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17db"},"rt":11644,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418090,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17dc"},"rt":6281,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424475,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17dd"},"rt":39925,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":464501,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B M Z Z F F E E E G O O 2M M M M X X N X 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17de"},"rt":26781,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491387,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"703 PMF F F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17df"},"rt":13814,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":505308,"subject":"FOMHO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38046","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"X X X X G G B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f0"},"rt":15668,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":49708,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z 5F F A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f1"},"rt":9732,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59585,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J J E E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f2"},"rt":22949,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82652,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"U C C C C Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f3"},"rt":6551,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89329,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"008 AM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMU U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f4"},"rt":63103,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152639,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O O O 12 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM04 PM05 PM04 PME H 6I O O I I 403 PM03 PME E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f6"},"rt":5217,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":160914,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"08 AME G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f7"},"rt":12656,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173658,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I I 32F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f8"},"rt":35662,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209422,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"12 PM2B 03 PM04 PMX B B I B I I J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17f9"},"rt":9593,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":219114,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"5M M J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17fa"},"rt":11680,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230886,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17fb"},"rt":4417,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235404,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"03 PM11 AM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17fc"},"rt":5019,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240512,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17fd"},"rt":24364,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":265006,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z Z Z X X O C C E E F F B B B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17fe"},"rt":19844,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284938,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X B B F F M X M M O M 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e17ff"},"rt":28608,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313903,"subject":"GXAV1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38608","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"I B O O X X X X F F E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1810"},"rt":17840,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":44648,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"1A U B B U U A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1811"},"rt":14594,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59338,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1812"},"rt":20344,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79799,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1813"},"rt":62789,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142694,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z Z F F O H F U F F F U 04 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1814"},"rt":39323,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182308,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"O O I I C I I 12 PMU A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1816"},"rt":8952,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":196894,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"08 AM09 AM09 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1817"},"rt":22692,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219683,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B F X N 05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1818"},"rt":83953,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303805,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L L L C B X X X G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1819"},"rt":25558,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":329615,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e181a"},"rt":22925,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352632,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X O X M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e181b"},"rt":7037,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359764,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e181c"},"rt":7293,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367164,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"I B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e181d"},"rt":118014,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":485270,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z M B J I F C C 02 PMX X B F 01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e181e"},"rt":27192,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":512776,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B 12 PMM M 02 PMJ I F F M J J J J X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e181f"},"rt":127123,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":640011,"subject":"PTMPD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41278","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J M M F F 02 PMF O X X 04 PMX A A E O O B O O B M M M J B O B B 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1830"},"rt":35526,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":63691,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"4A Z F A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1831"},"rt":12717,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76502,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"2A D D E E Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1832"},"rt":8360,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84956,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1833"},"rt":48404,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133453,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"03 PM04 PMU O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1834"},"rt":52451,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185997,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F I O O 02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1836"},"rt":5489,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":194306,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1837"},"rt":10531,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204928,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J I B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1838"},"rt":16715,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221752,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"4B B B F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1839"},"rt":13959,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":235800,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"X J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e183a"},"rt":30541,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266439,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F B B 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMF F E A G G B B B B B 03 PM04 PMX X X X C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e183b"},"rt":7449,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273979,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I I B B B F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e183c"},"rt":3442,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277515,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e183d"},"rt":46440,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":324047,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"X X H H Z Z X M M M B B O Z J J I J X B F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e183e"},"rt":24169,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348305,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PMO B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e183f"},"rt":23272,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371664,"subject":"YV5WY","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43015","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"02 PMX X F F E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1850"},"rt":23301,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":54887,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1851"},"rt":9354,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64359,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1852"},"rt":15100,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79578,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"U U Z C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1853"},"rt":21591,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101284,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"C Z 04 PME E 04 PM04 PMB H 04 PMH G B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1854"},"rt":44878,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146272,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,H ,D ,E ","hovered":"09 AMA O A A K H H H H H J E E D E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1856"},"rt":53343,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":201414,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ,L ","hovered":"M 09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PME E G L C H H L L D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1857"},"rt":50085,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251606,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"10 AM01 PMC X X X X O H O 01 PM01 PMB B B J J F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1858"},"rt":36038,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287754,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,K ","hovered":"G B B X X X M M M F F J A K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1859"},"rt":16595,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":304487,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O C C E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e185a"},"rt":6132,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310803,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F X 02 PMB E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e185b"},"rt":6796,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317705,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"03 PM02 PM12 PM12 PMM M M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e185c"},"rt":4748,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322594,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e185d"},"rt":8770,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":331472,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"302 PMF F E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e185e"},"rt":7355,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338936,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"12 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e185f"},"rt":59432,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398479,"subject":"LNEF7","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43280","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"X X X X C O O O 65X O O 02 PMX X X X X C C C X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1870"},"rt":101699,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":723946,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"309 AM08 AMI I I C C O O 11 AMC H Z F F F F F Z Z C 12 PMA F A A 11 AM11 AMA A A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1871"},"rt":13319,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":737592,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E D D D E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1872"},"rt":35113,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":772808,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"74C C C C C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1873"},"rt":70131,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":843040,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"C 05 PM12 PMZ C C C C C A F U U U U U F F 01 PMF F F 01 PMH H J J J U 02 PMU 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1874"},"rt":44607,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":887958,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I Z Z 11 AMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1876"},"rt":29162,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":922958,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1877"},"rt":125204,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1048274,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"H F F B B B F 10 AMB B B B F B B B B B B F B F B B X B F F X X X X O J J J J I I X X X X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1878"},"rt":62415,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1110989,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"L B B B 10 AMB B 11 AMB X J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1879"},"rt":18568,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1129906,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e187a"},"rt":2438,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1132456,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e187b"},"rt":3189,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1135789,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e187c"},"rt":3521,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1139422,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e187d"},"rt":10940,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1150471,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"O Z B F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e187e"},"rt":5747,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1156340,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e187f"},"rt":9320,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1165771,"subject":"0A9WN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34563","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1890"},"rt":20411,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":65830,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA A A 11 AMA 212 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1891"},"rt":16651,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82601,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H H D D E E E E E D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1892"},"rt":30555,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113278,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"C C C C U B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1893"},"rt":39278,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152662,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM03 PMA 04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM04 PMZ 11 AM11 AMJ J I I C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1894"},"rt":14503,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167267,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"7I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1896"},"rt":15811,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190914,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"10 AM10 AM10 AMJ B E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1897"},"rt":32494,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223523,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,J ,N ,X ","hovered":"F F H N N D D 10 AM11 AMJ J J X X D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1898"},"rt":22648,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246275,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"I B B B B B B X X M M J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1899"},"rt":17680,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":264060,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B M M M B B F F 1I B F I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e189a"},"rt":7503,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271667,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e189b"},"rt":9842,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281609,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J 10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PMB B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e189c"},"rt":7212,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288921,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e189d"},"rt":12866,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":301889,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"O 1I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e189e"},"rt":28601,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330628,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"J J I 01 PM03 PM02 PM11 AMC 03 PMO 03 PMC C C M O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e189f"},"rt":8674,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339413,"subject":"XV09T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41461","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"I 01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b0"},"rt":108090,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371602,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A A 12 PM11 AMZ Z 11 AM12 PM12 PMK K B A A F F O Z Z Z J H D D D D D D D D E G B K K K U U J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b1"},"rt":59004,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430914,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,D ","hovered":"F D D 04 PMD K U U U H J H F Z Z Z I O O A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b2"},"rt":39523,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470564,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"C C Z Z F U U K E G G G B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b3"},"rt":47182,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517874,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U Z Z Z Z F U O O I O H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b4"},"rt":44145,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562163,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"4F F F F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b6"},"rt":12339,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":609598,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"M X E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b7"},"rt":31908,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":641649,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"F M M M B F I I J J X O X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b8"},"rt":27996,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":669755,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G B B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18b9"},"rt":39046,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":708914,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"J J I B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18ba"},"rt":13758,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":722790,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18bb"},"rt":18754,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":741651,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ,X ","hovered":"M 12 PM12 PMX O H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18bc"},"rt":67302,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":809083,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"5B B B M M M M M C C C X X X X F F J J M M E F F B X X C C C G A H H L Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18bd"},"rt":35217,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":844605,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"Z 12 PM12 PMM M M M M F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18be"},"rt":31597,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":876323,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4O O P L L L H H H H H H H L P 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18bf"},"rt":12856,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":889297,"subject":"9Z01R","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d0"},"rt":13829,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117032,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d1"},"rt":18425,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135561,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J D E E E E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d2"},"rt":16429,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152077,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d3"},"rt":7863,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160028,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d4"},"rt":27922,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188043,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d6"},"rt":8136,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":204093,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d7"},"rt":12864,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217043,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d8"},"rt":36119,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253244,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"B B M M M J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18d9"},"rt":14241,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":267577,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18da"},"rt":19397,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287060,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18db"},"rt":10234,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297377,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18dc"},"rt":4806,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":302327,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18dd"},"rt":19281,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":321694,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18de"},"rt":20324,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342127,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18df"},"rt":16484,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":358693,"subject":"F6QWV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37997","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,E ","hovered":"B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f0"},"rt":24516,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85093,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"008 AM10 AM11 AMA C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f1"},"rt":9968,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":95177,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f2"},"rt":28787,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124082,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C A A A A 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f3"},"rt":14213,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138411,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PME D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f4"},"rt":30530,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169056,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"J I I I O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f6"},"rt":28640,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202913,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"C P P 7E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f7"},"rt":19577,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":222604,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C F B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f8"},"rt":126223,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348945,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"8F B B B B X C C F F F X X O O F F F O O O J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18f9"},"rt":22329,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":371567,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18fa"},"rt":7627,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379315,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"F F F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18fb"},"rt":15810,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395245,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C B B B B B F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18fc"},"rt":5082,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":400451,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18fd"},"rt":91507,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":492072,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,G ","hovered":"Z Z Z D 09 AM08 AMM M Z 04 PM03 PMG G G G A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18fe"},"rt":87003,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":579380,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"01 PM01 PMM X O O J J J E E I B X G X X X M X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e18ff"},"rt":74992,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":654666,"subject":"0AXM8","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32830","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J 09 AM01 PM02 PMX X X X C C C C M M X X X X B B F B B F B B J J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1910"},"rt":28349,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119609,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1911"},"rt":9659,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129387,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C A E 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1912"},"rt":10996,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140491,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C 10 AM10 AMC 10 AM11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1913"},"rt":35763,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176363,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PMU U U U U U H 01 PMF F 12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1914"},"rt":80702,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257171,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ,U ","hovered":"I I O O O O B U U 02 PM01 PMH H H H H 01 PMF 12 PM12 PMZ Z Z 12 PMO 11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1916"},"rt":7957,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270674,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1917"},"rt":13855,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284650,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1918"},"rt":33499,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":318252,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E L L F F B I I I B B E F F B 12 PM01 PM02 PMX X 02 PM01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1919"},"rt":17518,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335875,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I J J I I I 09 AM10 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e191a"},"rt":21346,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357330,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F F B B B B B B 04 PM02 PMX X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e191b"},"rt":6522,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363955,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e191c"},"rt":4774,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368843,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"1B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e191d"},"rt":25393,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":394354,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"C O H Z Z Z Z 03 PMO O 02 PM02 PMX X X 02 PM01 PM12 PMF F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e191e"},"rt":70990,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465451,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"X 03 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM02 PMX 01 PM01 PM11 AME E 11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PMX O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e191f"},"rt":38500,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504219,"subject":"S3JZD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41260","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X 02 PM01 PM12 PMB F B B 12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AME E E 11 AM11 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1930"},"rt":8801,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1460477,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"110 AM11 AM11 AMA 33"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1931"},"rt":6579,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1467491,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1932"},"rt":8134,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1475805,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1933"},"rt":48900,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1525252,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"K K 04 PME H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1934"},"rt":153978,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1679448,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"I U U U U U U U U U U X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1936"},"rt":45948,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1730816,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I J J M X X B B B F E E G G A A A E G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1937"},"rt":22189,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1753466,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1938"},"rt":47721,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1801934,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1939"},"rt":17605,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1819681,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I I J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e193a"},"rt":249502,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2069755,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"6F F F 04 PMZ O O 03 PM02 PM01 PMO F F B F 09 AM10 AMJ J J I E J J F B B F F 09 AMJ J 09 AM10 AME E E F M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e193b"},"rt":9363,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2080514,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e193c"},"rt":4788,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2085671,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e193d"},"rt":31032,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2116953,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"5Z Z Z Z X X Z X F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e193e"},"rt":28664,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2145722,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"7I O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e193f"},"rt":73392,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2219204,"subject":"XHMNM","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36519","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"X X X X X X X M X B B F 11 AM10 AMJ J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1950"},"rt":40561,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":87545,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A C A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1951"},"rt":5256,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92904,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1952"},"rt":8517,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101525,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C A A C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1953"},"rt":57152,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158773,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A K U F F F Z F F U U O Z F F U K A A A I I O G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1954"},"rt":57475,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216343,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"O O 12 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1956"},"rt":6463,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":226930,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"G G G G G E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1957"},"rt":15268,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242298,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1958"},"rt":26556,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268948,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L L G G J J B B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1959"},"rt":17372,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":286414,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I 3B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e195a"},"rt":19221,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305733,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"C O F 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PMX X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e195b"},"rt":5832,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311904,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e195c"},"rt":10249,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322246,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"H F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e195d"},"rt":39219,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":361564,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"O Z Z Z F B B M M Z O X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e195e"},"rt":20081,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381779,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O X 03 PMX B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e195f"},"rt":37730,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419606,"subject":"UV0QH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,E ","hovered":"F X B O O B M M F J J F E G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1970"},"rt":27690,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76886,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1971"},"rt":9297,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86299,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C A D D E E 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1972"},"rt":15375,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101785,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1973"},"rt":38338,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140231,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"C 03 PM04 PMU F F H Z Z A A O O H A 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1974"},"rt":105741,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246082,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I U U U U 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1976"},"rt":7902,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":259045,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1977"},"rt":12854,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272193,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1978"},"rt":58558,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330859,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F B B B A E E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1979"},"rt":24371,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":355337,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"4I J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e197a"},"rt":34712,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390241,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"04 PMF B B B B F Z 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e197b"},"rt":8669,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399225,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e197c"},"rt":4999,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":404332,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e197d"},"rt":26123,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":430561,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"M Z Z F F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e197e"},"rt":38135,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468808,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X B B O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e197f"},"rt":25808,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":494734,"subject":"T2MAH","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35606","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1990"},"rt":18885,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42923,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"J A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1991"},"rt":57589,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101927,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"11 AM01 PMA D D K U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1992"},"rt":18113,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120135,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"F A C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1993"},"rt":32305,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152614,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"C A F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1994"},"rt":180288,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333481,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"A I I I O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1996"},"rt":28529,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":368341,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"F E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1997"},"rt":17382,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385821,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,H ","hovered":"I C C C H H B B C H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1998"},"rt":11609,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397683,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"B M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1999"},"rt":12634,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":410447,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"2I B J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e199a"},"rt":87931,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":499060,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F Z Z F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e199b"},"rt":7267,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506590,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"201 PM12 PMF I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e199c"},"rt":6124,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":512809,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e199d"},"rt":18990,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":534077,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"Z Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e199e"},"rt":19399,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553575,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"12 PM05 PM04 PM03 PMB B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e199f"},"rt":7415,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561241,"subject":"WEFE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43223","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b0"},"rt":13836,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43924,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"08 AMC 11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b1"},"rt":10055,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":54093,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"U D K D D K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b2"},"rt":6594,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60775,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b3"},"rt":10832,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71707,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H F F Z 02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PME E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b4"},"rt":24221,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96017,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"H I I I G G B B B B B 01 PMF G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b6"},"rt":22985,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":121211,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"10 AM10 AMA G M M 09 AMJ 09 AMI I I I E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b7"},"rt":15757,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137063,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"G G G I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b8"},"rt":16592,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153763,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ","hovered":"C C F X X L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19b9"},"rt":24879,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":178751,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"G A B B B B B J E E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19ba"},"rt":13542,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192423,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"C X C X O F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19bb"},"rt":17855,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210473,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B B F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19bc"},"rt":2784,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213356,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19bd"},"rt":21141,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":234584,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,J ","hovered":"Z Z Z F Z Z Z Z O O O O O O O F F F 10 AMJ O B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19be"},"rt":3569,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238236,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19bf"},"rt":4501,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242825,"subject":"6TQE3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37633","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d0"},"rt":9258,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":47154,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d1"},"rt":21506,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68766,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"10 AM12 PMD E K 04 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d2"},"rt":15675,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84604,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"12 PMZ C 11 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d3"},"rt":19899,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":104602,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"12 PM04 PME E E E D D D 01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d4"},"rt":50075,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154773,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I O 12 PM12 PMZ O I I J J I O O A C 10 AM10 AMA A A Z 12 PM12 PM12 PMF U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d6"},"rt":11712,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":169822,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d7"},"rt":14171,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184089,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I J B B B F B B B B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d8"},"rt":28520,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212702,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"3B B E G G J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19d9"},"rt":14498,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":227297,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"12 PM01 PMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19da"},"rt":26948,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":254343,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F B B B B B F F I Z E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19db"},"rt":6990,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261426,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"311 AM12 PM12 PMB F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19dc"},"rt":4044,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265650,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19dd"},"rt":32377,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":298128,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"301 PM02 PMZ 04 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM12 PM12 PMM M M 11 AMF E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19de"},"rt":29177,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327413,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"01 PM01 PM01 PMI 10 AM11 AM11 AMJ X X B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19df"},"rt":16864,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344374,"subject":"ES98M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"12 PM02 PM02 PMX X B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f0"},"rt":143963,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250699,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A C C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f1"},"rt":27115,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278154,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H A E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f2"},"rt":28663,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306964,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f3"},"rt":24296,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":331419,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"K K U U U H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f4"},"rt":48341,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379932,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"8O O I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f6"},"rt":18042,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":404675,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f7"},"rt":19575,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424399,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C X X X F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f8"},"rt":15399,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439964,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,I ,J ","hovered":"B E I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19f9"},"rt":15558,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":455682,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"L J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19fa"},"rt":64342,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":520172,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B G L B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19fb"},"rt":14982,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535490,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"G M M B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19fc"},"rt":13932,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":549582,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19fd"},"rt":21044,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":570810,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"N Z O O C F Z Z B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19fe"},"rt":75290,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":646245,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F C X B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e19ff"},"rt":12228,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":658805,"subject":"OLFCD","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43175","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"F F F O O X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a10"},"rt":15141,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138439,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C 12 PMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a11"},"rt":8954,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147476,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"3K K E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a12"},"rt":11906,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159469,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"4C 11 AM12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a13"},"rt":12313,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171871,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"3U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a14"},"rt":53792,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225747,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"09 AM02 PM12 PM01 PM03 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a16"},"rt":7522,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243620,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a17"},"rt":15647,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259350,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a18"},"rt":35293,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294730,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a19"},"rt":14085,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":308903,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a1a"},"rt":78341,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387333,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F B B B 01 PM02 PMB B F B 12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM03 PM12 PM01 PMX I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a1b"},"rt":6276,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393926,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a1c"},"rt":4759,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398781,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"5B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a1d"},"rt":16024,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414892,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"L Z Z Z F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a1e"},"rt":42081,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457060,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PMX M M M B 12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a1f"},"rt":20794,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477947,"subject":"KW3D0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42585","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F M E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a30"},"rt":29407,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86978,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"510 AMZ Z Z Z 01 PMZ F A A C C F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a31"},"rt":13529,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100606,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"U 05 PM02 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a32"},"rt":17995,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118708,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"F C C C C A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a33"},"rt":26807,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145620,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a34"},"rt":33556,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179285,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J I I O O O J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a36"},"rt":110791,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":291503,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"09 AMG C 46E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a37"},"rt":59609,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351364,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F F F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a38"},"rt":152262,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":503737,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"9G G G G 12J G A G G G G G E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a39"},"rt":80261,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":584264,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"10 AMB J I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a3a"},"rt":55637,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":640148,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"08 AMF B B B B I M M M M X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a3b"},"rt":23507,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":663752,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F 02 PM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a3c"},"rt":24931,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":688791,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"E B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a3d"},"rt":47265,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":736165,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"7F X D Z Z 04 PMZ O X X M M O O B B F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a3e"},"rt":408417,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1144682,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O X M B B M M M E F B B M M B B B B B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a3f"},"rt":31691,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1176621,"subject":"Y82VR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41935","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"X O X 02 PMM M X X O M M C B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a50"},"rt":18107,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147033,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,H ,K ","hovered":"O O 4O O H O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a51"},"rt":6052,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153500,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a52"},"rt":7908,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161824,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,I ,J ","hovered":"I I J J D F E U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a53"},"rt":8015,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":170162,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a54"},"rt":5593,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176101,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,U ,G ","hovered":"G G K U U U U 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a56"},"rt":4452,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":186529,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,O ","hovered":"O O D D M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a57"},"rt":3463,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190275,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ,O ","hovered":"G O O 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a58"},"rt":4919,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195450,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,E ,G ","hovered":"G G E G G G G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a59"},"rt":4415,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":200142,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ,I ","hovered":"I B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a5a"},"rt":3120,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203607,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,E ,F ","hovered":"E F F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a5b"},"rt":4182,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208185,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,E ,H ","hovered":"E C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a5c"},"rt":2483,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211031,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,K ","hovered":"K A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a5d"},"rt":5498,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":216803,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,H ,Z ","hovered":"G C C C G G H H H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a5e"},"rt":4194,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221269,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ,I ","hovered":"I J J J B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a5f"},"rt":3169,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224723,"subject":"Z2J43","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35704","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,F ,O ","hovered":"C F O O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a70"},"rt":13632,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":39354,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"J J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a71"},"rt":8317,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":47795,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"10E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a72"},"rt":14365,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62281,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"U C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a73"},"rt":2782,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":65173,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a74"},"rt":7123,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":72404,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a76"},"rt":5686,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":83325,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ,H ","hovered":"H H H H G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a77"},"rt":10328,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":93757,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,H ","hovered":"G B B C C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a78"},"rt":8242,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102107,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ,L ","hovered":"L C C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a79"},"rt":9759,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":111973,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,N ","hovered":"P X X X N D N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a7a"},"rt":4346,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":116430,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C Z Z 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a7b"},"rt":4708,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":121243,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"F K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a7c"},"rt":6928,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128279,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"C C Z O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a7d"},"rt":4486,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":132872,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,G ","hovered":"G G G G G C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a7e"},"rt":3675,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136656,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ","hovered":"L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a7f"},"rt":4251,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141014,"subject":"WBJQG","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35436","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"E C C 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a90"},"rt":14302,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":74039,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A C C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a91"},"rt":19186,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":93358,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D D J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a92"},"rt":34303,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127783,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"H C C C C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a93"},"rt":46771,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174692,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"K C C 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a94"},"rt":23601,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198614,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"I I H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a96"},"rt":6989,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":214687,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a97"},"rt":20305,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235117,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C C C C F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a98"},"rt":26239,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261492,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a99"},"rt":16764,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":278385,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a9a"},"rt":14201,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292705,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"F F F F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a9b"},"rt":10531,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303379,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a9c"},"rt":6297,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":309809,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a9d"},"rt":12644,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":322586,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ","hovered":"E Z D D D N I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a9e"},"rt":49212,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371916,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"I 03 PM03 PMM X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1a9f"},"rt":12398,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":384438,"subject":"SLYYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42564","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"3J J M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab0"},"rt":25004,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237235,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"311 AMA A A A A 11 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab1"},"rt":7259,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244610,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"K E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab2"},"rt":11825,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257573,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab3"},"rt":23278,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281047,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,H ","hovered":"E H H E E H H J H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab4"},"rt":102998,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":384239,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"I H F F K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab6"},"rt":16150,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":447479,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab7"},"rt":67764,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515354,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab8"},"rt":62932,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":578633,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"A F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ab9"},"rt":109560,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":688511,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1aba"},"rt":68146,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":756970,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B B F F F B B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1abb"},"rt":10474,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767758,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"X X 12 PMB B B B B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1abc"},"rt":13936,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":781804,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"4B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1abd"},"rt":37087,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":819011,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,P ","hovered":"G F Z F G P H H Z P P P P P P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1abe"},"rt":37877,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":857004,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1abf"},"rt":222340,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1079981,"subject":"GGMWW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38988","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"X X X X X X X G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad0"},"rt":22785,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":91756,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad1"},"rt":25655,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117696,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"Z 01 PM12 PM11 AMD D E E E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad2"},"rt":29305,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147100,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"F C A 11 AMA A C A A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad3"},"rt":95853,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243056,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F 02 PM03 PM04 PME E E F F 4C A C C A 01 PMZ J H X X X X X J J H F F Z Z Z Z Z F Z A U U U U K K 03 PMK H H H J H F F 01 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad4"},"rt":646386,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":889830,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"H O H H I I 03 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMO O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad6"},"rt":141161,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1036336,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G B G G G E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad7"},"rt":12659,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1049329,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad8"},"rt":75848,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1125481,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"9I E E E J J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ad9"},"rt":17857,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1143654,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ada"},"rt":34338,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1178383,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F F Z B B M B F G C X X X J B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1adb"},"rt":11174,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1189846,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMB B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1adc"},"rt":5665,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1195797,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1add"},"rt":47160,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1243065,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B J F Z Z O O X X X B O O B Z F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ade"},"rt":30975,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1274152,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PMO O O B B O O B B F 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1adf"},"rt":86766,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1361110,"subject":"4BCUB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41696","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"J J 12 PM03 PM02 PMX X X X X J J M M 01 PMN B B B B X X X F E G G E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af0"},"rt":22167,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69316,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af1"},"rt":12817,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82243,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af2"},"rt":25140,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107471,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM05 PM06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af3"},"rt":38284,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145897,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af4"},"rt":29433,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175424,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af6"},"rt":145196,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327735,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"3N 05 PMM 01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM07 PMX X C C C C M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af7"},"rt":55558,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383553,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ,L ","hovered":"O X X X X K H 02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM08 PMO H L X X X K 02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM08 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM07 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af8"},"rt":84654,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468516,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"6B B 02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM06 PM05 PME E E E E X 03 PM04 PMX G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1af9"},"rt":14917,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":483845,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1afa"},"rt":58629,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542613,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F X X X X M O B O O C E G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1afb"},"rt":7602,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550379,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"510 AM11 AM01 PM12 PMB B F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1afc"},"rt":8845,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559316,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M M B B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1afd"},"rt":105576,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":664986,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B X Z F F O O F G H C C B B B X M M B B B 12 PMB 01 PM02 PM03 PMO X M M C E 11 AM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM12 PMX 03 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1afe"},"rt":45809,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":711063,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX X X 02 PM03 PM04 PMO B 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMB B F M F E 12 PM11 AM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM01 PMI G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1aff"},"rt":96231,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":807391,"subject":"11NFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40795","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,E ,F ","hovered":"I 01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMM J 10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMX J 11 AM12 PMM M B 01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMB B B F B B 12 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMF F F E 01 PM02 PME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b10"},"rt":21283,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":91755,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b11"},"rt":13721,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105591,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E G E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b12"},"rt":27830,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133535,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"10 AMC Z Z 3Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b13"},"rt":66553,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200202,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z U K H H J J O O O A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b14"},"rt":137457,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337983,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"11 AMO O I I 03 PM03 PMU 03 PMK E A A F F H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b16"},"rt":7915,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":350112,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b17"},"rt":25978,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":376207,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B M M M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b18"},"rt":35742,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412064,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"L B B G E G F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b19"},"rt":14455,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":426633,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b1a"},"rt":36398,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463148,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"Z 04 PMO X Z Z O O O G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b1b"},"rt":8458,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":471726,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b1c"},"rt":16310,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":488154,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b1d"},"rt":47325,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":535598,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z 04 PMX X X O O X B O O B M B F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b1e"},"rt":36499,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572210,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B O B B F F G 02 PM03 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b1f"},"rt":19529,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591859,"subject":"WF1M3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30445","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,C ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM02 PMX X B C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b30"},"rt":43727,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69166,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"D 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A 11 AMO O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b31"},"rt":9432,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78708,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O E 04 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b32"},"rt":25058,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":103862,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C C C C A A Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b33"},"rt":34492,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138452,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"E 04 PM04 PMC A A Z U U U U U U K K H H J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b34"},"rt":201035,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339583,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"H I I I H H H H K K K F U Z Z Z K K H I I I F A A A F F K O K E D H E U U E U U H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b36"},"rt":5875,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":349054,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b37"},"rt":49918,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399073,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F F Z Z B B 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b38"},"rt":49253,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448425,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C F F B B E E G G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b39"},"rt":26036,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":474554,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"5F C M J B I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b3a"},"rt":54095,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528741,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"O F Z 04 PMG G E E G G C F Z Z 04 PMF F B O I B X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b3b"},"rt":5963,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534802,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b3c"},"rt":9323,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":544230,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B O O F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b3d"},"rt":32019,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":576346,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"F Z 04 PMZ F Z Z B B M M X X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b3e"},"rt":108762,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":685201,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PMC E B B B G G X X 05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PMF F B B B O X X M B E E M M M B O 03 PMM B O X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b3f"},"rt":47803,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":733262,"subject":"MCJ0W","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40345","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AMX 02 PM02 PMX 02 PMX B 02 PMB X X X X F F F G G G X X E C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b50"},"rt":18506,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88082,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A U A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b51"},"rt":11236,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99415,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"K D D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b52"},"rt":24878,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124379,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b53"},"rt":9149,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133617,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b54"},"rt":22439,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156141,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"H I O O F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b56"},"rt":8015,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":168093,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"09 AMP E E E G G G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b57"},"rt":13066,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181245,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b58"},"rt":30343,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211673,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"E B J J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b59"},"rt":18387,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230145,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I J J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b5a"},"rt":20109,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250347,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F Z O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b5b"},"rt":4863,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255295,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b5c"},"rt":3472,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258851,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b5d"},"rt":25872,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":284809,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"Z Z F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b5e"},"rt":14001,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298901,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b5f"},"rt":30909,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329895,"subject":"XJLSB","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37251","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"X B I I F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b70"},"rt":18718,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":52392,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AMA 11 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b71"},"rt":17577,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70083,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F J E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b72"},"rt":8439,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78633,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b73"},"rt":29712,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108451,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"A 04 PM04 PME D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b74"},"rt":14736,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":123302,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,I ","hovered":"O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b76"},"rt":6168,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":136113,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"09 AME E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b77"},"rt":16395,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152624,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b78"},"rt":64549,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217291,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"7E B X X X X I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b79"},"rt":13812,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231389,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b7a"},"rt":32004,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263501,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B 12 PM12 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b7b"},"rt":9107,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272707,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b7c"},"rt":4757,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277568,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b7d"},"rt":38510,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":316174,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"06 PMP P P 04 PMF F 11 AME B X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b7e"},"rt":97417,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413692,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M M X J J J B B M X X O 03 PMA J J J J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b7f"},"rt":55862,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469843,"subject":"FFHE0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36224","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"I M M F E G G A K C X X C C C C F B B I I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b90"},"rt":12820,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64179,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AMA O A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b91"},"rt":16949,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81225,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A Z D D D J J E J J D D D 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PMD E E 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b92"},"rt":25578,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106910,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C A Z Z A A C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b93"},"rt":37983,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144992,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PM04 PME U 5C C A Z Z O O O O O I F F F F F H H U K 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b94"},"rt":87088,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232176,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"7I I I O O O O O 12 PM01 PM02 PMK K K E O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b96"},"rt":7517,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":247525,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b97"},"rt":15485,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263109,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b98"},"rt":38202,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301410,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E B B I I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b99"},"rt":25857,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327377,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"Z H O N N X J J J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b9a"},"rt":29289,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356760,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F B B 12 PMB F F 03 PM04 PMX C B B F F O J F F G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b9b"},"rt":12206,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369060,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I I 11 AM12 PMM 12 PMM B B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b9c"},"rt":6833,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375993,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"G C F B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b9d"},"rt":21826,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":397910,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"8H Z Z 04 PMX X F B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b9e"},"rt":26918,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424927,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M B J J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1b9f"},"rt":48889,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473911,"subject":"3N5PQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"X B M M B B F F E E J J M M A 01 PMC X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb0"},"rt":23457,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99323,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb1"},"rt":8582,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108016,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"6E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb2"},"rt":11754,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119877,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb3"},"rt":42583,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162570,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"B B 04 PME E K U U U H F F Z Z Z F O 11 AM11 AMO O O I A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb4"},"rt":46861,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209546,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"O 11 AMU U U H 01 PMH H H H J F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb6"},"rt":8499,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":223556,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb7"},"rt":15983,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239652,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B F F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb8"},"rt":28737,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268503,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"8B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bb9"},"rt":14439,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":283055,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"10 AMJ J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bba"},"rt":16598,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299767,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F 12 PMF M M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bbb"},"rt":8226,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308104,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bbc"},"rt":5938,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314156,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"4B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bbd"},"rt":71537,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":385803,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"X H Z Z Z Z M F 01 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bbe"},"rt":44788,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430918,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F X M M F F E E X X M M M F B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bbf"},"rt":36220,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467245,"subject":"R8SJJ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39420","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMJ M M M B B 12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd0"},"rt":26757,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136987,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"8J J 12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A A O A 11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd1"},"rt":7740,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144932,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd2"},"rt":10387,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155489,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd3"},"rt":58651,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214311,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"03 PMU F F O O A A 12 PMZ 01 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd4"},"rt":97661,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312138,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"5H I O O O 01 PMF U U A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd6"},"rt":6711,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":324383,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"08 AM122E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd7"},"rt":17489,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342201,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd8"},"rt":20566,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362952,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bd9"},"rt":20123,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":383252,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bda"},"rt":71063,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454465,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B F F F Z F G F F F E F B B B F B B F B B B F F M M C C C C G J J J I B Z Z O O X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bdb"},"rt":7177,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462243,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"4411 AM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bdc"},"rt":6706,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469095,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bdd"},"rt":28106,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":497366,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"6Z Z O X X X Z G G G F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bde"},"rt":75061,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572574,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMX J I B B B B O O C F Z G C G G C C C C C 08 AM08 AMJ M X X B O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bdf"},"rt":85484,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":658521,"subject":"7OBDZ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32998","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M 02 PMJ B B O O E G G G F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf0"},"rt":45031,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162421,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,F ","hovered":"A A C A F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf1"},"rt":24056,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":186580,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,K ","hovered":"D D K A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf2"},"rt":25868,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212541,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ,E ","hovered":"C C U U E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf3"},"rt":33073,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245700,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"K B A U U U E U U E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf4"},"rt":100523,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346310,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"A Z Z Z I 09 AM09 AMC O I O O I O Z Z I H H F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf6"},"rt":9456,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":360036,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf7"},"rt":102035,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462157,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M M B B C M M M M D F B B M I B B B F F M X O N N N Z Z H H H Z N N N B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf8"},"rt":89048,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":551467,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B B B B F G F F A F B B X X J E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bf9"},"rt":20485,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":572226,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"5F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bfa"},"rt":27756,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600073,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"B F J I 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bfb"},"rt":7676,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607837,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"2F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bfc"},"rt":6581,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":614506,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bfd"},"rt":25326,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":639928,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z X X X Z O O O O B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bfe"},"rt":31940,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671954,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X X B B 11 AMJ B B M X X X O M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1bff"},"rt":62568,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":734614,"subject":"3QQX3","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39648","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"5X X O O O X M B B F F F F E A E F F B B M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c10"},"rt":8151,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184361,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c11"},"rt":11000,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195473,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A O D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c12"},"rt":7772,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203357,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"008 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c13"},"rt":18076,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221543,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,U ","hovered":"08 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMU F F Z Z O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c14"},"rt":35291,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256947,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"03 PM04 PMI 11 AMU H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c16"},"rt":8623,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275765,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PME G E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c17"},"rt":18492,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294367,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c18"},"rt":24764,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319286,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c19"},"rt":16254,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335653,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c1a"},"rt":49944,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385709,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F F F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PMF X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c1b"},"rt":20060,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405877,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"11 AMB B B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c1c"},"rt":10518,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416512,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c1d"},"rt":24669,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":441298,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"N Z Z O 04 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c1e"},"rt":31717,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473135,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PMX X X M M M M B B B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c1f"},"rt":140354,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":613632,"subject":"XYGF1","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37688","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"3X X X X F B F M 01 PMM 12 PM11 AMX X B B F F 12 PMM B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c30"},"rt":43160,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126442,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AMA A C C F F F C 11 AMA 10 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c31"},"rt":11636,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138289,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"C H H H J K K O 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c32"},"rt":22150,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160681,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"C C C O O O O O A O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c33"},"rt":14338,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175310,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"404 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c34"},"rt":14330,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189830,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"H I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c36"},"rt":31066,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230507,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I I I J B 09 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F F 12 PM11 AM12 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c37"},"rt":61841,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292848,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"11 AM11 AM12 PMB B B M 01 PM12 PM01 PMO O N N N O X 08 PM07 PM07 PM06 PM06 PM05 PM05 PM04 PMZ H H H H H L H X X 01 PM01 PMM B F F 11 AMB B F H H H L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c38"},"rt":51978,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345354,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,O ","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM12 PM11 AM12 PM02 PM03 PMC G G F F B B B X X O O O O I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c39"},"rt":11008,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356534,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,I ","hovered":"J J J J I I F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c3a"},"rt":20270,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377016,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,Z ","hovered":"5B F F F F B F F F Z F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c3b"},"rt":14580,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391855,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"7701 PMB B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c3c"},"rt":11943,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403995,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F B B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c3d"},"rt":32268,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":436451,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ,L ","hovered":"O X I Z Z Z Z Z Z H H H Z Z H H L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c3e"},"rt":11775,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448418,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM03 PML L H 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c3f"},"rt":12795,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461393,"subject":"9T8HW","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42968","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMK X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c50"},"rt":16259,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97060,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"12 PM11 AMA A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c51"},"rt":8473,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105632,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E E E C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c52"},"rt":27974,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133701,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C A A C A Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c53"},"rt":30646,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164439,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U U 03 PM04 PM04 PMU U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c54"},"rt":102839,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267367,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I O O 12 PMF H H J H H E E D D I I H 11 AMH J I E E E D D D E E J F F F H H U U H K K Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c56"},"rt":9297,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":312770,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c57"},"rt":14452,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327327,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c58"},"rt":41979,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369413,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G G B J J I B M E G I I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c59"},"rt":29554,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399274,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c5a"},"rt":28491,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427872,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"N N O B F B B Z X X X X X F 01 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c5b"},"rt":7525,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435496,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c5c"},"rt":6388,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441987,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"Z Z H G B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c5d"},"rt":14167,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":456257,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z F F X X X X X F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c5e"},"rt":49894,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506245,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O 03 PM03 PMX B 04 PM03 PMX X X X B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c5f"},"rt":50005,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":556349,"subject":"NU1ZQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43282","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"O O O X O O X M 01 PM02 PMX X F F F F E E E F F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c70"},"rt":35115,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107981,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"88411 AMF F F F 08 AMZ F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c71"},"rt":6853,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114919,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"10 AMA D K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c72"},"rt":19097,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134103,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"09 AMC 09 AM09 AMC A 10 AM09 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c73"},"rt":13479,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147670,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"05 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PMH H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c74"},"rt":14360,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162117,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"H I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c76"},"rt":22847,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":194403,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"I B I B O B B I B O O E E E G G I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c77"},"rt":27002,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221482,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"B F F F X X O X O 03 PM02 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c78"},"rt":51356,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272919,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"A G F F F B C F J J J G G 10 AMC C C J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c79"},"rt":79803,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352812,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"C J J B F J B J 12 PM12 PM10 AMI I E E E B B B B F I I J B 10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c7a"},"rt":11477,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364529,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"5F E F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c7b"},"rt":7582,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":372192,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"12 PMM L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c7c"},"rt":10262,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":382544,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c7d"},"rt":8881,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":391505,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"C Z 02 PMF E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c7e"},"rt":10869,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402460,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c7f"},"rt":9226,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411768,"subject":"64VZS","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27100","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"02 PMX X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c90"},"rt":78703,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122667,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"C A A 10 AM11 AM11 AMZ F F A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c91"},"rt":38203,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161124,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"09 AM12 PME D K K K 05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c92"},"rt":13856,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175278,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"4F F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c93"},"rt":6409,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181771,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"U 06 PM05 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c94"},"rt":51092,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232951,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c96"},"rt":8042,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":247596,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"O E G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c97"},"rt":29702,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277387,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"O O X X X X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c98"},"rt":83417,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360890,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"E B 12 PMB B 12 PMG G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c99"},"rt":26778,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387925,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"I I B B 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c9a"},"rt":8597,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396611,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c9b"},"rt":14554,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411254,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"11 AM11 AM12 PMM F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c9c"},"rt":13967,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425310,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c9d"},"rt":21055,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":446453,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"C C N N Z Z F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c9e"},"rt":12824,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459359,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1c9f"},"rt":15125,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474568,"subject":"3SG1K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34070","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"02 PMX X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb0"},"rt":26524,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79143,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb1"},"rt":10047,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89354,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"A U U E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb2"},"rt":105093,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194607,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C O O C C C C C C O J A A A C C C C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb3"},"rt":39988,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234931,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"Z Z A Z U A Z Z Z H H A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb4"},"rt":92242,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327319,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,U ","hovered":"A U O O O O E E J J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb6"},"rt":24639,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":360963,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"76E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb7"},"rt":64821,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425927,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"E E C F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb8"},"rt":36891,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463153,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cb9"},"rt":34416,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":497725,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cba"},"rt":38241,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":536114,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F Z Z Z X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cbb"},"rt":10701,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":546955,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cbc"},"rt":8383,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":555497,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cbd"},"rt":35338,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":590975,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"X X B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cbe"},"rt":34883,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":626013,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PM03 PMX O O B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cbf"},"rt":49673,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":675827,"subject":"OW65D","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M X X F F F F F F G G X X X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd0"},"rt":14405,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284602,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd1"},"rt":21530,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306344,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"U E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd2"},"rt":18967,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325624,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C 10 AMC C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd3"},"rt":17627,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343406,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd4"},"rt":28019,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371564,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,Z ","hovered":"C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd6"},"rt":10620,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":391424,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd7"},"rt":109182,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500995,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,M ","hovered":"I I J B F F C I C H H O M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd8"},"rt":120234,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622009,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"9B X X N X X F E F F G I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cd9"},"rt":25634,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":648094,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cda"},"rt":22738,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":670954,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"3F F B B 12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AMJ B B 12 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cdb"},"rt":9747,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":681130,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cdc"},"rt":10602,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":692080,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"I O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cdd"},"rt":28240,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":720607,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z X X M B B F C J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cde"},"rt":56086,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":776848,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PMB 12 PMB B B 12 PMJ J M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cdf"},"rt":84778,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":861796,"subject":"N31JV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41909","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf0"},"rt":18349,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":72487,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"76E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf1"},"rt":7224,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79812,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"J D D D X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf2"},"rt":19414,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99329,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"U U C C C C C C C J O O C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf3"},"rt":21028,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120453,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,G ","hovered":"G K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf4"},"rt":15861,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136412,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"D D F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf6"},"rt":14006,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":164390,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf7"},"rt":24214,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188700,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,H ","hovered":"C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf8"},"rt":19750,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208632,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,K ","hovered":"B E B B A G K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cf9"},"rt":27994,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":236802,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cfa"},"rt":25120,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262023,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"5F Z Z F G Z G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cfb"},"rt":8029,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270150,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"02 PM01 PMM M M M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cfc"},"rt":9412,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279658,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cfd"},"rt":39436,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":319193,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z 3I F Z B F F F Z O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cfe"},"rt":9806,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329097,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1cff"},"rt":33138,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362337,"subject":"3H75M","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41659","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,I ,O ","hovered":"Z O O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d10"},"rt":27099,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129816,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z Z Z Z A A 12 PM01 PMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d11"},"rt":7172,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137120,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d12"},"rt":14672,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151907,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C A C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d13"},"rt":60358,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212388,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"U U E E D D D 04 PM04 PMC E E D Z Z A A C 04 PM06 PM05 PMU U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d14"},"rt":164407,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377194,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"C A C A A H U U U U H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d16"},"rt":10326,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":397778,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"10 AMJ I E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d17"},"rt":18968,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416866,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I F F B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d18"},"rt":46752,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463748,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"J J I E E E I I 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d19"},"rt":22240,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":486428,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I I J I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d1a"},"rt":47925,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534475,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"N F B B F F F B B 12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMF I F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d1b"},"rt":8290,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542905,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"B M M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d1c"},"rt":5163,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":548194,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d1d"},"rt":35646,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":583965,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z X O C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d1e"},"rt":17866,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":601949,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X 05 PM04 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d1f"},"rt":339106,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":941200,"subject":"B8HA2","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35289","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F B B B M M M X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d30"},"rt":19534,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":63659,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"1A A A A A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d31"},"rt":10490,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":74249,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"O E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d32"},"rt":47107,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":121439,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d33"},"rt":28517,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150127,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"C E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d34"},"rt":40603,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190808,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,D ","hovered":"O O O I J J D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d36"},"rt":9080,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":208995,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d37"},"rt":19382,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228808,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d38"},"rt":42952,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271902,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E 11 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d39"},"rt":12350,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":284408,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"09 AM08 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d3a"},"rt":20722,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305209,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d3b"},"rt":9323,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314705,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d3c"},"rt":9371,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324162,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d3d"},"rt":41641,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":366001,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z X F X 03 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d3e"},"rt":47096,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413198,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"03 PMB E E E M M M M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d3f"},"rt":85089,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498775,"subject":"GYGOR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36823","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M C C G G 01 PME E E E F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d50"},"rt":22345,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85852,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d51"},"rt":8314,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":94263,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"Z C K E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d52"},"rt":47979,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142347,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"C C C A U K B B B K K K G B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d53"},"rt":29401,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171846,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,H ","hovered":"K J J H H 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d54"},"rt":9938,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181878,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d56"},"rt":17414,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":207096,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G G H 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d57"},"rt":17886,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225078,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d58"},"rt":102775,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327945,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B F F F F F E I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d59"},"rt":24712,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352961,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"5I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d5a"},"rt":111332,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464393,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F Z Z Z Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d5b"},"rt":11768,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476426,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B B B B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d5c"},"rt":4641,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481193,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d5d"},"rt":17006,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498293,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"B Z F F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d5e"},"rt":66172,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564556,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d5f"},"rt":44874,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":609690,"subject":"7SV52","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42819","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"X X X X M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d70"},"rt":34460,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96526,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A 11 AMA C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d71"},"rt":10817,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107458,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d72"},"rt":11784,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119363,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C C Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d73"},"rt":20154,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140140,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F Z Z Z A C C F U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d74"},"rt":64942,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205423,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"4C K K I O O O O I I H H H H H H O O I H H F F U U 02 PMU U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d76"},"rt":8701,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233927,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d77"},"rt":15391,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249454,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d78"},"rt":22045,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271616,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E F F B B B B F B B E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d79"},"rt":22970,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":294701,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I I 10 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d7a"},"rt":34361,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329172,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"B B M M G G E J F B B B M X X X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d7b"},"rt":13986,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343268,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d7c"},"rt":8198,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351587,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d7d"},"rt":18538,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370263,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z Z O X E E E F B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d7e"},"rt":17334,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387758,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M B M M M M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d7f"},"rt":21789,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409658,"subject":"S4EK0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38143","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M M B B F F E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d90"},"rt":15534,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":912039,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d91"},"rt":32183,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":944309,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E U D D 08 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d92"},"rt":12464,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":956868,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C 02 PM01 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d93"},"rt":11818,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":968773,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"04 PMU U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d94"},"rt":62218,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1031077,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"H O I A A 11 AM03 PM03 PMF F F F F O I I I H H O U F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d96"},"rt":7657,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1150429,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"P G E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d97"},"rt":16203,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1166717,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d98"},"rt":27007,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1193821,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d99"},"rt":122725,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1316637,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"E H L X X J J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d9a"},"rt":28334,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1345206,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d9b"},"rt":10710,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1355998,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M M M B B F F F B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d9c"},"rt":5399,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1361486,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d9d"},"rt":31984,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1393557,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"F M G G 03 PM05 PM04 PM04 PMX X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d9e"},"rt":30092,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1423733,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O 03 PM03 PMG G F X X B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1d9f"},"rt":97643,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1521462,"subject":"KQBZN","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42906","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"H X X X B B B B B B B M M X X F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db0"},"rt":28067,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":61289,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"5I 510 AM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db1"},"rt":11462,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":72845,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db2"},"rt":39826,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112769,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"A C C C C C C C A A Z Z 10 AM12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db3"},"rt":29975,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142841,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"E E D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db4"},"rt":18901,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161849,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db6"},"rt":17999,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":183600,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"J E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db7"},"rt":32527,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216223,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C C F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db8"},"rt":88300,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304624,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"G B B I I J J J I I B I E E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1db9"},"rt":36391,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":341301,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"76J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dba"},"rt":48506,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389903,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z X M F F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dbb"},"rt":8573,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398575,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"02 PM12 PMB B B B F 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dbc"},"rt":6543,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405215,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"Z F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dbd"},"rt":15117,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":420438,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z F X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dbe"},"rt":117533,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538078,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"O 03 PMO B B B B B B F M X 03 PM03 PMO F F F J I M M J J X X X X O 03 PM03 PMI O O O O B B B O B 12 PM12 PM12 PMB B O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dbf"},"rt":41802,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580169,"subject":"WEG15","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37764","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"Z B J 12 PM02 PMX X E G G X X X E E E X F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd0"},"rt":30733,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86118,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd1"},"rt":33878,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120308,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"D D 03 PM01 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd2"},"rt":13482,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133906,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd3"},"rt":27143,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161409,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PME 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd4"},"rt":20472,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182023,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd6"},"rt":14204,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":198545,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"F 02 PM01 PME E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd7"},"rt":132042,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330803,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F 46C H H H H G F F F J J J J I J J B F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd8"},"rt":40617,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":372197,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"E E E J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dd9"},"rt":11622,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":383962,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dda"},"rt":13050,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397139,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ddb"},"rt":10072,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407339,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ddc"},"rt":16827,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424289,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"C F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ddd"},"rt":31449,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":455863,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"Z Z Z H H H H O O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dde"},"rt":22963,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":478943,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"E H 04 PM03 PMO O O O O O 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ddf"},"rt":17032,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496099,"subject":"6XY80","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"01 PMX X K K X X X X 1X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df0"},"rt":10808,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62160,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"10 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df1"},"rt":27318,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89608,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"08 AM5D E D 04 PMD D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df2"},"rt":20346,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":110101,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df3"},"rt":39411,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":149668,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,U ","hovered":"C C A A Z Z Z Z F F O O O O I F U U H K K B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df4"},"rt":67956,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217751,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"I I I I A C A A F H H H F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df6"},"rt":7244,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231932,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"44E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df7"},"rt":25793,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257851,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F B B B Z F I B O J J J X N D M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df8"},"rt":19606,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277597,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1df9"},"rt":21434,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299150,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dfa"},"rt":25266,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324551,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"O G G M M B O L L F B B B B F M M M M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dfb"},"rt":9008,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333682,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"10 AM12 PM01 PMB B B F F F F F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dfc"},"rt":7755,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341559,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dfd"},"rt":35566,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377251,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"C Z O X X C M M B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dfe"},"rt":19716,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397109,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M B B F B J J J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1dff"},"rt":37391,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":434671,"subject":"RD6JR","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36415","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"M M B B F B B F F E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e10"},"rt":26019,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48819,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"O O F 12 PMH O H H F A 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e11"},"rt":6831,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55754,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e12"},"rt":10814,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66696,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C A Z Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e13"},"rt":33109,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99911,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"502 PM01 PMK I F F U U U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e14"},"rt":29848,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129855,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"E E E E U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e16"},"rt":6082,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":139447,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e17"},"rt":15800,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155339,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e18"},"rt":23275,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178711,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,I ,J ,M ","hovered":"E F F I J B O X M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e19"},"rt":30841,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":209657,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"3J I I 12 PM11 AMI 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e1a"},"rt":15954,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225732,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"Z Z O X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e1b"},"rt":6059,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231898,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e1c"},"rt":2834,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234831,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e1d"},"rt":17277,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":252213,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"5Z Z F X X X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e1e"},"rt":15930,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268245,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M X O O O B B Z O J 22"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e1f"},"rt":19034,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287424,"subject":"OFP8T","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30000","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"B X X O O B Z F B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e30"},"rt":14568,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62376,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C 65A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e31"},"rt":8458,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70971,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"H E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e32"},"rt":26490,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97584,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"45E O C C A A A C C C A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e33"},"rt":28091,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125796,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"A Z 03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PMU J F 10 AM09 AM10 AMC C 01 PM02 PM04 PME U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e34"},"rt":103376,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229298,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"A I I I I I O O I I I H H O O J H H 01 PMH I I I O A 11 AMI B B B B G U U X Z Z F O K O O J 01 PM01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e36"},"rt":7878,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":240580,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E E G 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e37"},"rt":12644,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253344,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"J F B N D 06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e38"},"rt":66089,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319552,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"7L C B B X 02 PMX X J I I 12 PME E E E E E 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMO F B B B O O X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e39"},"rt":14229,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":334384,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J J I X N D X 10 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e3a"},"rt":33794,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368295,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F Z Z F F B B X F B B B B B M M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e3b"},"rt":9581,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377993,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"5F N B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e3c"},"rt":10620,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388728,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e3d"},"rt":59490,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":448335,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"N N Z F F B B M O O O C I E E F C G G G X X 11 AM4Z N N O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e3e"},"rt":21075,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469531,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"603 PMM M B X B B B 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e3f"},"rt":102402,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572053,"subject":"MXPYU","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40257","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"F F F E I E E C B B B M G G A E I I B B M M M M B I B E J J N J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e50"},"rt":17190,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92306,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AMA A A A 11 AMA A 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e51"},"rt":13239,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105663,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E E E E G 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e52"},"rt":16678,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122461,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e53"},"rt":37214,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159798,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"F F H H H I A Z Z F F F F H J U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e54"},"rt":125815,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285736,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I I I I O O 12 PM12 PMO F F Z U F I I O O 12 PM12 PM11 AMC F F F O F A A A A F F F F F F H H H J H H U U U U U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e56"},"rt":10858,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":302094,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"5E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e57"},"rt":16233,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":318450,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C 4F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e58"},"rt":51358,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369922,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C C B I I I I I I I E E E E X F E E E E E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e59"},"rt":32437,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":402479,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J I I I I J J I 10 AM10 AM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e5a"},"rt":21326,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423931,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F F F F F 12 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMB I M M X B B B 12 PM12 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e5b"},"rt":11244,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435288,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M M M B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e5c"},"rt":11037,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446453,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e5d"},"rt":29606,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":476173,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"X X B B F F B 12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e5e"},"rt":9498,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":485782,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"12 PMB B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e5f"},"rt":268690,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":754588,"subject":"TMVAO","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38545","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"11I I I J J J 12 PMB F M X J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e70"},"rt":82658,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148217,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,F ","hovered":"A A 1C A C Z Z Z Z 10 AM09 AMI J H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e71"},"rt":41023,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189498,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"K K X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e72"},"rt":55994,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245622,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"U A Z Z F 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMF Z 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e73"},"rt":16351,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262089,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"2Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e74"},"rt":17003,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279202,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"H O O I O O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e76"},"rt":8054,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":293593,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e77"},"rt":27774,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321465,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"6J J 10 AMF F F M X O 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e78"},"rt":43371,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364934,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"7G F B J F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e79"},"rt":36332,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":401359,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"I E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e7a"},"rt":12258,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413703,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F F F F E 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e7b"},"rt":12357,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426147,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L ,M ","hovered":"4M M L I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e7c"},"rt":12481,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438721,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"F G F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e7d"},"rt":18563,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":457398,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e7e"},"rt":15441,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472945,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X X 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e7f"},"rt":20724,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":493790,"subject":"1JPFK","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38651","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e90"},"rt":27755,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":94853,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AMC 12 PM11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e91"},"rt":13366,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108331,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e92"},"rt":8290,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":116859,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e93"},"rt":10158,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127167,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ","hovered":"E E D D J D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e94"},"rt":13471,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140759,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e96"},"rt":28665,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":175866,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"311B B E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e97"},"rt":13949,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190029,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,Z ","hovered":"I F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e98"},"rt":49009,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239285,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ,M ","hovered":"B B E F F I I J J I I I M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e99"},"rt":14334,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253883,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e9a"},"rt":26666,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280835,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"F I I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e9b"},"rt":8579,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289630,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e9c"},"rt":4943,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294904,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"X B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e9d"},"rt":32647,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327785,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"G Z X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e9e"},"rt":19070,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347023,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1e9f"},"rt":16265,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363401,"subject":"Q10C6","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"M 02 PM02 PMX X K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb0"},"rt":28626,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113551,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"09 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb1"},"rt":17076,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130727,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb2"},"rt":15563,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146397,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"08 AM08 AM108 AM10 AMA A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb3"},"rt":24547,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171059,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"06 PM05 PM04 PMK K 04 PM04 PM10 AM09 AM10 AM12 PMK K K 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb4"},"rt":12779,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183947,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ,H ","hovered":"H H H J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb6"},"rt":20028,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":213730,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ,K ,L ,P ","hovered":"K A A A L C C C A C C C C P A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb7"},"rt":35001,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248846,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"01 PMJ J J M M M X N D N D D 03 PMN N X X M M B B I I B B B 10 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMM M M M I I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb8"},"rt":49090,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298035,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"J J 02 PM11 AM08 AM09 AM04 PM08 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PMM M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eb9"},"rt":28747,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":326887,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"12 PM09 AMC H F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eba"},"rt":9592,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":336579,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"I 01 PM11 AMB B B B F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ebb"},"rt":13624,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350299,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M ","hovered":"J 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMX M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ebc"},"rt":18132,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368528,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"B B B B Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ebd"},"rt":11634,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":380257,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"O Z X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ebe"},"rt":12544,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392901,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"202 PM03 PM02 PMJ D O O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ebf"},"rt":4928,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397923,"subject":"SCYR0","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed0"},"rt":20724,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":73872,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"C C C C A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed1"},"rt":8259,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82233,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed2"},"rt":27743,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":110075,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"C C C C 10 AM11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed3"},"rt":30274,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140549,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"I H B G G 04 PMX K U F F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed4"},"rt":40227,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":180882,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"I I I I U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed6"},"rt":7696,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":196621,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"09 AME G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed7"},"rt":8582,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205310,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed8"},"rt":32392,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237807,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"B I I J J J J X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ed9"},"rt":20934,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":258847,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J ","hovered":"J J I I I I I J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eda"},"rt":23009,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281958,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"F Z O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1edb"},"rt":11857,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293928,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"M M B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1edc"},"rt":10949,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304978,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"C F B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1edd"},"rt":25544,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":330620,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,X ","hovered":"X Z X Z Z F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ede"},"rt":22123,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352847,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"M 03 PM03 PMO B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1edf"},"rt":32909,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385862,"subject":"GQX64","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ","hovered":"01 PM01 PM02 PMX X F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef0"},"rt":13559,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2766412,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"O O A A A A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef1"},"rt":5736,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2772254,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"U D E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef2"},"rt":15903,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2788261,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"G G C C C C A Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef3"},"rt":25635,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2814152,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"K K U U U U K K U A A A A I O O O F O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef4"},"rt":11994,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2826239,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"I I O 10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef6"},"rt":5396,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2833754,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"F E G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef7"},"rt":13312,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2847214,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"F J I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef8"},"rt":4243,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2851545,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1ef9"},"rt":8019,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2859763,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ","hovered":"B B F F B B B C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1efa"},"rt":9993,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2869848,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"B O B F F F X O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1efb"},"rt":7302,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2877247,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B M B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1efc"},"rt":5347,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2882684,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1efd"},"rt":10173,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2893059,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,G ","hovered":"F H H H G F F H H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1efe"},"rt":12896,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2906188,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,E ","hovered":"F B I F B F E E E E 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1eff"},"rt":16133,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2922470,"subject":"JA76O","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40762","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ,J ","hovered":"I M M M C O I I I B B B F F B B J J J O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f10"},"rt":13097,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53706,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"Z Z 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f11"},"rt":12590,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66399,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f12"},"rt":23973,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90487,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z ","hovered":"01 PM01 PMA C C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f13"},"rt":8400,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98984,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"05 PM04 PMD E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f14"},"rt":29103,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128197,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H ","hovered":"I J 06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PMO O O O H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f16"},"rt":6811,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":139353,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f17"},"rt":10887,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150355,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"C C F F F B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f18"},"rt":20670,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171117,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"7B F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f19"},"rt":10388,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":181604,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"B B B B O O O J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f1a"},"rt":21450,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203173,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"7F F Z Z Z Z Z G H X X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f1b"},"rt":6016,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209289,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f1c"},"rt":5252,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214646,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f1d"},"rt":34345,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":249086,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"X X H Z Z Z Z H Z Z G G G H H O X X X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f1e"},"rt":9421,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258608,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X ","hovered":"11 AM12 PM03 PM04 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f1f"},"rt":20458,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279169,"subject":"NOXYV","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42474","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,M ","hovered":"02 PMX B M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f30"},"rt":20807,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84241,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"11 AMA A A C A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f31"},"rt":15622,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99989,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"C J E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f32"},"rt":46149,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146270,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"U C A A F A A Z Z Z 10 AMC C C A A U U A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f33"},"rt":20185,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166585,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"04 PME E E E 4E E E E D 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f34"},"rt":23672,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190390,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I I O O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f36"},"rt":6283,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":198417,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,G ","hovered":"E 5C C G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f37"},"rt":31989,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230533,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"I J J J F Z Z Z Z B 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f38"},"rt":27607,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258268,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"J B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f39"},"rt":19928,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":278337,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I ","hovered":"X J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f3a"},"rt":5617,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284091,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f3b"},"rt":6020,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":290231,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"12 PMB F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f3c"},"rt":9224,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299584,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f3d"},"rt":95495,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":395212,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ,X ","hovered":"H H Z Z Z Z H Z Z O O O Z Z Z Z O 03 PMO X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f3e"},"rt":57202,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452756,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O ","hovered":"I I 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMO O 03 PM03 PMP P P P P P 03 PMO O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f3f"},"rt":37812,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490703,"subject":"O9K5K","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41924","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,X ","hovered":"X X X X X J J M M J K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f50"},"rt":19222,"condition":"11115","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127175,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A ","hovered":"I 47O F 011 AMA A A C F 07 PM07 PM06 PM05 PMZ 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f51"},"rt":11181,"condition":"11115","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138445,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"Z F Z D D E 04 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f52"},"rt":24234,"condition":"11115","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162749,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ","hovered":"I A C J K K K K K K K K K 03 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f53"},"rt":8448,"condition":"11115","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171270,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,E ","hovered":"O 02 PM04 PME E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f54"},"rt":45267,"condition":"11115","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216614,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U ","hovered":"7I I I I J O J J J U U 03 PMI U U U U U E E E K K I I U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f56"},"rt":27926,"condition":"11115","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":276463,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ,F ","hovered":"F E E E E E F G F F 03 PM02 PMB B B O O O X X F X X O H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f57"},"rt":36511,"condition":"11115","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313052,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K ,L ","hovered":"J I E 5C P P P K L G K K K A A A G G G O O O X X X X K L L L K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f58"},"rt":56828,"condition":"11115","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369959,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E ","hovered":"B B J J J J J X O O O H H I I E E E F B J J J J A J J J B F F B B 12 PME E X B B E E E B E E F I E E G G E B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f59"},"rt":47652,"condition":"11115","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":417681,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O O O H J 10 AM09 AM08 AMM M J J J I I I I I E F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f5a"},"rt":55437,"condition":"11115","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473190,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G ","hovered":"C P P P P P G G K K K K K K A A G G C C G G K A A A A G G C C G G K K G G G G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f5b"},"rt":9659,"condition":"11115","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482925,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ,F ","hovered":"B X 02 PM12 PMB F B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f5c"},"rt":7342,"condition":"11115","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490338,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B ","hovered":"4F B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f5d"},"rt":79014,"condition":"11115","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":569425,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D ,N ","hovered":"5C C Z Z H Z Z Z Z Z H Z N N N N Z Z Z D D D D Z Z Z Z N N N N N D Z F D D D D D D D N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f5e"},"rt":34155,"condition":"11115","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603798,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F ,G ","hovered":"C F E 03 PM04 PMF F F F G F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc88307cc1f9a239e1f5f"},"rt":67624,"condition":"11115","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"5","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":true,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671490,"subject":"9PH05","study":"SGC5A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43303","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C ,G ","hovered":"12 PM02 PM02 PMX X A G C C X X X X A A A L "}]
